[Script Info]
Title:诸神字幕
Original Script:诸神字幕组
Original Timing:Maize
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:960
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: CN_OP,方正准圆_GBK,37,&H00F4FBDD,&H00FBF3EF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,1,2,2,0,0,7,1
Style: JP_ED,方正准圆_GBK,33,&H00FEE8FE,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DAC5DC,&H007F7F7F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,50,1
Style: CN_ED,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00F9E1F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9E1F3,&H005F5F5F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,10,1
Style: CN,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,5,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FEF0F2,&H00FBF3EF,&H00FCF7F6,&H00FFFBFA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H00FEF0F2,&H00FBF3EF,&H00800000,&H00800000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,2,2,0,0,10,1
Style: JP,MS Gothic,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,40,128
Style: disclaimer,方正准圆_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,20,134
Style: JP-furigana,MS Gothic,14.5,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,0,0,40,128
Style: JP_ED-furigana,方正准圆_GBK,16,&H00FEE8FE,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DAC5DC,&H007F7F7F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 1,0:01:47.73,0:01:49.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,インターハイ県予選を 勝ち進んだ湘北は
Dialogue: 1,0:01:50.42,0:01:52.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いよいよ 全国大会への出場を懸け
Dialogue: 1,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決勝リーグ第1戦で 海南大附属と対戦することになった
Dialogue: 1,0:01:57.41,0:01:58.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,己…
Dialogue: 1,0:02:05.36,0:02:07.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,てめぇには負けねえぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過去16年 連続インターハイ出場と
Dialogue: 1,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圧倒的強さを誇る王者 海南
Dialogue: 1,0:02:17.07,0:02:19.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その前評判は 今年も高かったが
Dialogue: 1,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽を倒して 決勝リーグ進出を決めた湘北も
Dialogue: 1,0:02:23.07,0:02:25.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,台風の目として注目を集めていた
Dialogue: 1,0:02:42.22,0:02:43.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何て子たちなの
Dialogue: 1,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始 数秒で 観衆のどぎもを抜いた
Dialogue: 1,0:02:48.34,0:02:52.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試合は 序盤から 一気に熱を帯びていった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:03:08.35,0:03:09.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4番 オーケー
Dialogue: 1,0:03:13.44,0:03:14.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5番 マーク
Dialogue: 1,0:03:15.45,0:03:16.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,9番 オーケー
Dialogue: 1,0:03:22.73,0:03:25.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北 マンツーマンか
Dialogue: 1,0:03:25.84,0:03:28.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この大会 ほとんど そうですね
Dialogue: 1,0:03:28.80,0:03:32.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ええ 湘北には マンツーマンが合ってる気がするわ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:35.01,0:03:37.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただ一つ 気がかりは
Dialogue: 1,0:03:38.41,0:03:39.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ポイントガード
Dialogue: 1,0:03:41.57,0:03:43.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,16cmの身長差
Dialogue: 1,0:03:43.76,0:03:46.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体重でも 20Kgもの差がある
Dialogue: 1,0:03:47.94,0:03:50.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宮城 牧のミスマッチ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:52.64,0:03:53.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高砂
Dialogue: 1,0:03:53.65,0:03:55.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ホントだ 簡単に上を
Dialogue: 1,0:04:00.08,0:04:01.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先取点は 海南だ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:07.47,0:04:08.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旦那
Dialogue: 1,0:04:08.37,0:04:09.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいぞ ゴリ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:09.81,0:04:10.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハエたたき
Dialogue: 1,0:04:10.81,0:04:12.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスブロック お兄ちゃん
Dialogue: 1,0:04:12.74,0:04:14.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いくぞ 速攻
Dialogue: 1,0:04:18.24,0:04:19.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ点が入らないぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:19.84,0:04:21.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すげえ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:22.50,0:04:25.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速攻だ 今度は 湘北 チャンス
Dialogue: 1,0:04:26.08,0:04:29.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この速い攻めで 湘北は勢いづいてくる
Dialogue: 1,0:04:30.53,0:04:33.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北 得意のラン アンド ガン オフェンスよ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:33.85,0:04:35.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いけ！湘北
Dialogue: 1,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三井 3点か
Dialogue: 1,0:04:47.10,0:04:48.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おおっ もう戻ってる
Dialogue: 1,0:04:50.60,0:04:51.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘えよ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:56.59,0:04:57.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うまい
Dialogue: 1,0:04:57.55,0:05:00.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3ポイントだけじゃねえんだ あの人は
Dialogue: 1,0:05:02.28,0:05:03.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先取点 もらった
Dialogue: 1,0:05:11.58,0:05:12.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧
Dialogue: 1,0:05:19.54,0:05:20.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし！
Dialogue: 1,0:05:25.87,0:05:26.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よっしゃ！
Dialogue: 1,0:05:30.22,0:05:31.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南のカウンターだ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:32.10,0:05:33.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2対2よ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:40.22,0:05:41.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ 来やがれ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:44.04,0:05:44.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清田に付け
Dialogue: 1,0:05:45.83,0:05:48.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かってらい 指図すんな 偉そうに
Dialogue: 1,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川 神の3ポイント 気を付けろ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:51.99,0:05:52.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打ってくるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:05.74,0:06:06.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打つ気か
Dialogue: 1,0:06:15.01,0:06:16.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスパス
Dialogue: 1,0:06:17.82,0:06:19.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘いな 野猿
Dialogue: 1,0:06:22.26,0:06:23.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食らえ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:24.40,0:06:25.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴリ直伝
Dialogue: 1,0:06:27.17,0:06:29.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハエたたき
Dialogue: 1,0:06:48.51,0:06:49.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何!?
Dialogue: 1,0:06:56.99,0:07:00.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,また抜かれた もっと スピード出せへんの 中村君
Dialogue: 1,0:07:02.31,0:07:03.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全第一
Dialogue: 1,0:07:05.75,0:07:08.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう この調子じゃ 試合が終わっちゃうじゃないの
Dialogue: 1,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大体 僕らだけで 陵南 対 武里戦まで
Dialogue: 1,0:07:12.27,0:07:14.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取材するなんて あんまりっすよ 相田さん
Dialogue: 1,0:07:15.14,0:07:16.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,働かせ過ぎだ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:16.99,0:07:20.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しょうがないでしょ スタッフ 少ないんだから
Dialogue: 1,0:07:21.33,0:07:24.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく1分でも無駄にはできないわ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:24.52,0:07:25.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛ばしなさい
Dialogue: 1,0:07:25.64,0:07:27.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は…はい
Dialogue: 1,0:07:32.60,0:07:33.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清田信長
Dialogue: 1,0:07:38.25,0:07:41.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南も とんでもない逸材を 見つけたもんね
Dialogue: 1,0:07:52.25,0:07:54.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンズアップや 越野さん
Dialogue: 1,0:08:04.50,0:08:05.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスカット
Dialogue: 1,0:08:06.16,0:08:07.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仙道君
Dialogue: 1,0:08:07.80,0:08:10.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で あの高さで取られるんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:15.44,0:08:17.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスパス いかすわ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:18.17,0:08:19.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アンビリーバブル
Dialogue: 1,0:08:19.73,0:08:21.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で あんなパスができるんや
Dialogue: 1,0:08:28.20,0:08:31.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっという間に 2点 取った
Dialogue: 1,0:08:31.48,0:08:32.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陵南 強い
Dialogue: 1,0:08:32.92,0:08:34.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こりゃ 止めようがないぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:34.26,0:08:36.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決勝リーグなのに 圧倒的じゃねえか
Dialogue: 1,0:08:36.53,0:08:37.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごいぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:41.42,0:08:42.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弟さんですか
Dialogue: 1,0:08:42.60,0:08:44.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僕 中村といいます
Dialogue: 1,0:08:44.37,0:08:46.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相田さんには いつも お世話になってます
Dialogue: 1,0:08:47.21,0:08:48.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やめんか
Dialogue: 1,0:08:48.61,0:08:49.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね…姉ちゃん
Dialogue: 1,0:08:52.10,0:08:56.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彦一 あんたも頑張って 早う仙道君みたいになってや
Dialogue: 1,0:08:56.39,0:08:59.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほっといてや 早う 記者席 行かな 怒られんで
Dialogue: 1,0:09:18.81,0:09:22.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年は 同じベスト4の陵南と武里
Dialogue: 1,0:09:35.04,0:09:38.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1年間で こんなにも差がついたのね
Dialogue: 1,0:09:53.05,0:09:54.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ 湘北 点が取れない
Dialogue: 1,0:09:54.64,0:09:56.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱ 清田のあのダンク 効いてるぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:56.88,0:09:58.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダメージは大きい
Dialogue: 1,0:10:02.02,0:10:04.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くそっ どうした 湘北
Dialogue: 1,0:10:04.85,0:10:06.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかりしろ 花道
Dialogue: 1,0:10:25.32,0:10:27.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの野郎
Dialogue: 1,0:10:31.97,0:10:33.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見てたぜ 翔陽戦
Dialogue: 1,0:10:33.80,0:10:36.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダンク 決める気分ってのは どんなだ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:37.26,0:10:39.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さすが有名人
Dialogue: 1,0:10:39.77,0:10:41.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前には分かるまい
Dialogue: 1,0:10:51.92,0:10:53.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この桜木を
Dialogue: 1,0:10:56.44,0:10:58.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こけにしやがったな
Dialogue: 1,0:11:32.37,0:11:33.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このままじゃ まずいわ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:36.47,0:11:39.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここは 何としても ついていかないと
Dialogue: 1,0:11:40.71,0:11:42.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく まず1本だ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:45.18,0:11:45.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミッチー！
Dialogue: 1,0:11:45.61,0:11:47.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待ってました ミッチー
Dialogue: 1,0:11:58.38,0:11:59.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし いけ！赤木
Dialogue: 1,0:12:05.34,0:12:06.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘い
Dialogue: 1,0:12:08.74,0:12:09.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿！
Dialogue: 1,0:12:09.53,0:12:10.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うそ！
Dialogue: 1,0:12:10.50,0:12:10.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばかな
Dialogue: 1,0:12:11.14,0:12:13.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何て高さだ あの10番
Dialogue: 1,0:12:20.13,0:12:21.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴリ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:22.63,0:12:23.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし いいぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:23.67,0:12:24.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やった
Dialogue: 1,0:12:24.61,0:12:25.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ついに出た
Dialogue: 1,0:12:25.96,0:12:27.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴリラダンク
Dialogue: 1,0:12:27.17,0:12:28.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お兄ちゃん さすが
Dialogue: 1,0:12:35.33,0:12:36.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どっちがだ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:38.62,0:12:40.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ざまあ見ろ 野猿め
Dialogue: 1,0:12:47.69,0:12:48.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:12:50.92,0:12:53.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前の役目を忘れるんじゃねえぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:57.08,0:12:57.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいな
Dialogue: 1,0:12:59.49,0:13:00.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴリ…
Dialogue: 1,0:13:14.09,0:13:15.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やってやろうじゃんか
Dialogue: 1,0:13:18.27,0:13:19.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決勝リーグ第1戦
Dialogue: 1,0:13:20.04,0:13:22.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南大附属 対 湘北
Dialogue: 1,0:13:23.20,0:13:26.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,序盤 予想に反して 湘北が大健闘
Dialogue: 1,0:13:30.26,0:13:32.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主砲 赤木の 気迫の籠もったプレーで
Dialogue: 1,0:13:32.99,0:13:34.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王者 海南に食らいつき
Dialogue: 1,0:13:34.99,0:13:37.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4点以上のリードを許さない
Dialogue: 1,0:13:40.40,0:13:42.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして 前半10分
Dialogue: 1,0:13:47.84,0:13:50.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おっしゃ！オフェンスリバウンド 取ったぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:13:51.35,0:13:54.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし 桜木 一旦 戻せ 立て直すぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:01.28,0:14:04.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし じっくり もう1本 いこう
Dialogue: 1,0:14:04.39,0:14:06.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいぞ 桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:14:06.35,0:14:07.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスリバン
Dialogue: 1,0:14:16.71,0:14:18.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木の あのリバウンドは
Dialogue: 1,0:14:19.10,0:14:21.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今や うちに欠かせない戦力に なってきましたね
Dialogue: 1,0:14:22.21,0:14:22.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 1,0:14:23.38,0:14:25.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南相手にも通用してますよ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:27.29,0:14:28.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうですね
Dialogue: 1,0:14:40.40,0:14:41.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おっしゃ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:43.82,0:14:45.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おらおらー！
Dialogue: 1,0:14:54.40,0:14:56.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くそっ 待て
Dialogue: 1,0:15:05.33,0:15:06.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳んだ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:13.19,0:15:13.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイス
Dialogue: 1,0:15:16.44,0:15:17.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危ない
Dialogue: 1,0:15:22.87,0:15:23.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木君
Dialogue: 1,0:15:24.08,0:15:24.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 1,0:15:25.20,0:15:26.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫か
Dialogue: 1,0:15:32.95,0:15:34.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ あの元気さは
Dialogue: 1,0:15:34.86,0:15:36.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,けが一つ してねえ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:36.86,0:15:38.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫ですか 先生
Dialogue: 1,0:15:41.02,0:15:43.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,監督をクッションにするとは
Dialogue: 1,0:15:44.91,0:15:46.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐ろしいやつ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:50.66,0:15:52.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よく走る
Dialogue: 1,0:15:55.33,0:15:58.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運動量だけなら 牧をも しのぐぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:58.83,0:16:01.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3か月の この桜木君は
Dialogue: 1,0:16:13.59,0:16:14.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 1,0:16:14.44,0:16:15.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,また取った
Dialogue: 1,0:16:17.72,0:16:20.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見よ リバウンド王の実力を
Dialogue: 1,0:16:21.16,0:16:22.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面白い
Dialogue: 1,0:16:22.78,0:16:25.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10番 俺がマークしてやる
Dialogue: 1,0:16:28.86,0:16:29.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧さん
Dialogue: 1,0:16:30.07,0:16:32.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おおー ついに 神奈川ナンバー1プレーヤー
Dialogue: 1,0:16:32.59,0:16:34.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧をもその気にさせちまった
Dialogue: 1,0:16:39.32,0:16:40.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君 何年
Dialogue: 1,0:16:42.24,0:16:43.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高校生
Dialogue: 1,0:16:43.70,0:16:45.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ば…ばか野郎
Dialogue: 1,0:16:45.18,0:16:47.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 野猿！ずるいぞ てめぇら
Dialogue: 1,0:16:47.63,0:16:49.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OBを連れてくるとは ひきょう者
Dialogue: 1,0:16:49.95,0:16:51.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばかか てめぇは
Dialogue: 1,0:16:51.17,0:16:53.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧さんは これでも れっきとした高3だ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:53.95,0:16:55.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,17歳だぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:55.39,0:16:57.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何 17
Dialogue: 1,0:17:02.23,0:17:04.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何が 17歳だ だまされるか
Dialogue: 1,0:17:04.96,0:17:05.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この野猿
Dialogue: 1,0:17:06.56,0:17:10.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試合中だぞ 私語は慎みなさい 両チームとも
Dialogue: 1,0:17:10.68,0:17:11.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どあほう
Dialogue: 1,0:17:14.28,0:17:15.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今回は警告だが
Dialogue: 1,0:17:15.48,0:17:17.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次からは 没収試合にもなりうるから
Dialogue: 1,0:17:18.13,0:17:19.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気を付けるように
Dialogue: 1,0:17:19.33,0:17:20.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特に 両方の10番
Dialogue: 1,0:17:21.19,0:17:23.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どあほうは 死ななきゃ治らない
Dialogue: 1,0:17:24.38,0:17:25.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やれやれ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:26.59,0:17:27.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,困ったもんです
Dialogue: 1,0:17:33.07,0:17:35.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの牧をこけにするとは
Dialogue: 1,0:17:35.91,0:17:37.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木だからな
Dialogue: 1,0:17:38.23,0:17:40.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怖いもの知らずの1年が
Dialogue: 1,0:17:41.05,0:17:42.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知らねえぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:46.75,0:17:48.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤木の方が老けてるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:49.58,0:17:50.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧…
Dialogue: 1,0:17:55.90,0:17:57.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そういえば
Dialogue: 1,0:17:57.34,0:17:58.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見るな
Dialogue: 1,0:17:59.60,0:18:01.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気にしてたのか
Dialogue: 1,0:18:01.94,0:18:03.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来い 桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:18:03.07,0:18:05.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう！いくぞ じい
Dialogue: 1,0:18:16.45,0:18:18.34,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ どうなってるかしら
Dialogue: 1,0:18:32.20,0:18:35.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴール下は 俺が制す
Dialogue: 1,0:18:38.29,0:18:41.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1年の桜木に あの牧が付いてる
Dialogue: 1,0:18:41.03,0:18:43.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じい！くっそー
Dialogue: 1,0:18:44.25,0:18:45.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスブロック 牧さん
Dialogue: 1,0:18:46.41,0:18:47.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神！
Dialogue: 1,0:18:48.47,0:18:49.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待て
Dialogue: 1,0:18:55.91,0:18:56.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,6点差だ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:56.97,0:18:58.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差が開きだしたぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:58.13,0:18:59.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さすが 海南
Dialogue: 1,0:19:00.25,0:19:02.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くそっ じいめ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:03.75,0:19:04.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 1,0:19:05.97,0:19:07.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ やってみろ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:07.71,0:19:09.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし 桜木ってやつは
Dialogue: 1,0:19:09.68,0:19:12.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南の牧相手でも 物おじしないな
Dialogue: 1,0:19:12.81,0:19:15.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く見てる方が怖くなってくるよ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何せ 入学早々 あの赤木先輩に けんか売った男だからね
Dialogue: 1,0:19:22.98,0:19:26.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧さん自らマークするまでもないっすよ こんな無礼者
Dialogue: 1,0:19:26.71,0:19:27.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この俺が！
Dialogue: 1,0:19:28.93,0:19:32.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前なんかにゃ この俺でも もったいなすぎるけどな
Dialogue: 1,0:19:33.18,0:19:34.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野猿
Dialogue: 1,0:19:35.21,0:19:35.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 1,0:19:36.93,0:19:37.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10番 オーケー
Dialogue: 1,0:19:47.71,0:19:48.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何!?
Dialogue: 1,0:19:49.45,0:19:50.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やった
Dialogue: 1,0:20:00.29,0:20:03.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今のは 全然 わざとらしくなかったぞ 花道
Dialogue: 1,0:20:03.48,0:20:04.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,リョーちん
Dialogue: 1,0:20:08.38,0:20:10.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,計算外の選手に かき回されて
Dialogue: 1,0:20:10.71,0:20:13.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽はペースを乱した
Dialogue: 1,0:20:16.06,0:20:18.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴子さん やった！
Dialogue: 1,0:20:19.02,0:20:21.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいぞ 花道
Dialogue: 1,0:20:21.86,0:20:23.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスフェイク
Dialogue: 1,0:20:24.29,0:20:25.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごい 桜木君
Dialogue: 1,0:20:32.41,0:20:34.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,予想外の大健闘で
Dialogue: 1,0:20:34.14,0:20:37.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北は 王者 海南に食らいつく
Dialogue: 1,0:20:41.36,0:20:44.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして 絶好調の桜木花道に対して
Dialogue: 1,0:20:45.44,0:20:48.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南の監督 高頭が動いた
Dialogue: 1,0:20:52.99,0:20:56.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼には 蚊帳の外にいてもらおうかな
Dialogue: 1,0:22:41.26,0:22:43.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ あの小さい変なやつは
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.63,0:22:47.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宮益！神と交代だ できるだけ 桜木を挑発するんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:48.13,0:22:49.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも ディフェンスは 何もしなくていい
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.11,0:22:53.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごいジャンプ力や リバウンドに 惑わされちゃいかん
Dialogue: 1,0:22:53.69,0:22:56.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼は あくまで3か月 素人だ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:56.39,0:22:59.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くそっ てめぇは張り合いが なさすぎるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:59.34,0:23:00.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やる気 あんのか こら
Dialogue: 1,0:23:01.27,0:23:04.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「SLAMDUNK」「桜木封じの秘密兵器！」
Dialogue: 1,0:23:04.77,0:23:05.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見てくれよな！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:49.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功晋级高中联赛县预赛决赛的湘北篮球队
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.42,0:01:52.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在决赛中 跟海南大附属碰头
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展开了争夺全国大赛出赛权的第一场战役
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.41,0:01:58.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.36,0:02:07.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会输给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去十六年来连续打进全国高中联赛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以压倒性的实力称霸全县的王者球队海南
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.07,0:02:19.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年他们的呼声仍然是一片高涨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是打倒翔阳 打进决赛周的湘北篮球队
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.07,0:02:25.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也像台风眼一样的 聚集了众人的注目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.22,0:02:43.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些孩子真了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛开始还没几秒 就让观众看得目瞪口呆的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:52.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全场的气氛已经完全热烈起来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.67,0:02:59.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计算之外？！花道状态一流！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.35,0:03:09.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四号 OK！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.44,0:03:14.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五号 盯住了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.45,0:03:16.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九号 OK！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.73,0:03:25.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北… 一对一紧盯人…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.84,0:03:28.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们好像每一场比赛 都是这个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.80,0:03:32.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用一对一紧盯人 比较合他们的个性
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.01,0:03:37.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有一点 令我相当的在意…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.41,0:03:39.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是控球后卫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.57,0:03:43.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身高差了16公分
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.76,0:03:46.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体重也相差快20公斤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.94,0:03:50.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫城跟阿牧的实力 相差太悬殊了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.64,0:03:53.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高砂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.65,0:03:55.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 这么简单就传过去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:01.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南会先得分的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.47,0:04:08.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队长
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.37,0:04:09.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩！干得好！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.81,0:04:10.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苍蝇拍球
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.81,0:04:12.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打得好啊！哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.74,0:04:14.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要上了！速攻！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.24,0:04:19.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有人得半分
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.84,0:04:21.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.50,0:04:25.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速攻！ 这次换湘北的机会了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.08,0:04:29.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这次快攻看来 湘北会趁势得分
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.53,0:04:33.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是湘北最拿手的 跑轰战术
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.85,0:04:35.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北 上啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三井他会拿到三分吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.10,0:04:48.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.60,0:04:51.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.59,0:04:57.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.55,0:05:00.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三井他不是只会投三分球而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.28,0:05:03.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先拿分的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.58,0:05:12.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.54,0:05:20.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.87,0:05:26.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.22,0:05:31.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南反击了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.10,0:05:33.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是二对二啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.22,0:05:41.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.04,0:05:44.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯好清田
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.83,0:05:48.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 用不着你来指挥我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川 小心阿神投出三分球
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.99,0:05:52.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要出手了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.74,0:06:06.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想投篮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.01,0:06:16.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传得好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.82,0:06:19.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太天真了 野猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.26,0:06:23.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.40,0:06:25.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩的真传
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.17,0:06:29.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苍蝇拍球
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.51,0:06:49.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.99,0:07:00.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又被超前了 中村难道你就不能再开快一点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.31,0:07:03.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交通安全最重要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.75,0:07:08.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到的时候比赛老早就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只派我们俩个人来采访陵南对抗武里的比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.27,0:07:14.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在太过份了 相田小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.14,0:07:16.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这简直是折磨人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.99,0:07:20.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么办法呢 谁叫人手不足
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.33,0:07:24.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之现在是分秒必争
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.52,0:07:25.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开快一点吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.64,0:07:27.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.60,0:07:33.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清田信长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.25,0:07:41.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南也找到了不可小看的人才
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.25,0:07:54.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越野 高传吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.50,0:08:05.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,截的好！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.16,0:08:07.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是仙道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.80,0:08:10.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球传的那么高 为何他接的到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.44,0:08:17.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传得漂亮 太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.17,0:08:19.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.73,0:08:21.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们怎么会做出那么漂亮的传球
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.20,0:08:31.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子就拿到两分
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.48,0:08:32.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陵南好强啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.92,0:08:34.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本就阻截不了耶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.26,0:08:36.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是决赛 但却一面倒的被攻下了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.53,0:08:37.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厉害了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.42,0:08:42.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是令弟吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.60,0:08:44.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫中村
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.37,0:08:46.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常常受到相田小姐的照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.21,0:08:48.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再说了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.61,0:08:49.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.10,0:08:56.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彦一 你也要好好的加油 早日像仙道一样那么厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.39,0:08:59.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你少管我 快点去做你的记者好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.81,0:09:22.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年同样是前四强的陵南跟武里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.04,0:09:38.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于短短一年 就出现这么大的差距了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.05,0:09:54.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北到现在还没有得分
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.64,0:09:56.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清田的灌篮好吓人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.88,0:09:58.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这打击真大
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.02,0:10:04.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶…你们到底是怎么搞的 湘北
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.85,0:10:06.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作点啊！花道！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.32,0:10:27.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.97,0:10:33.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔阳的比赛我看过了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.80,0:10:36.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灌篮成功的心情怎么样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.26,0:10:39.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我果然是个名人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.77,0:10:41.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远都不会知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.92,0:10:53.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把我樱木…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.44,0:10:58.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当个白痴耍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.37,0:11:33.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去可不妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.47,0:11:39.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要想办法赶上才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.71,0:11:42.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要先入球才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.18,0:11:45.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 三井！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.61,0:11:47.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 小三
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.38,0:11:59.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤木看你的了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.34,0:12:06.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天真
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.74,0:12:09.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.53,0:12:10.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.50,0:12:10.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.14,0:12:13.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个十号怎么能够跳那么高
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.13,0:12:21.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.63,0:12:23.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.67,0:12:24.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.61,0:12:25.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得分了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.96,0:12:27.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩灌篮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.17,0:12:28.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真棒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.33,0:12:36.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说谁天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.62,0:12:40.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活该 野猴子！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.69,0:12:48.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱木！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.92,0:12:53.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忘了你自已的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.08,0:12:57.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.49,0:13:00.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.09,0:13:15.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会给你好看的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.27,0:13:19.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决赛的第一场比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.04,0:13:22.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南大附属对抗湘北
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.20,0:13:26.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛刚开始 湘北的表现出人预料的精彩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.26,0:13:32.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在赤木气势逼人的球技跟带领下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.99,0:13:34.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王者海南大附属被咬住不放
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.99,0:13:37.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差距一直没有办法超过四分
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.40,0:13:42.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在前半场的十分钟！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.84,0:13:50.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 我们抢到篮板球了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.35,0:13:54.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱木 抢得好 回去就重整气势
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.28,0:14:04.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢来取一分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.39,0:14:06.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好啊！樱木
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.35,0:14:07.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抢得太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.71,0:14:18.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱木的那个篮板球
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.10,0:14:21.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经成了我们篮球队不可缺少的一支战力了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.21,0:14:22.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教练
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.38,0:14:25.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连海南队也没有办法抵挡他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.29,0:14:28.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的很对
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.40,0:14:41.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.82,0:14:45.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.40,0:14:56.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶站住
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.33,0:15:06.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.19,0:15:13.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.44,0:15:17.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.87,0:15:23.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱木！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.08,0:15:24.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.20,0:15:26.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.95,0:15:34.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那精力究竟是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.86,0:15:36.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没有受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.86,0:15:38.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要紧吧 教练
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.02,0:15:43.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然把教练当作垫子来用
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.91,0:15:46.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可怕的家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.66,0:15:52.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跑得可真快
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.33,0:15:58.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单比运动量已经超越阿牧了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.83,0:16:01.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只打了三个月篮球的樱木…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.59,0:16:14.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.44,0:16:15.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又抢到了…！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.72,0:16:20.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧！ 这就是篮板王的实力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.16,0:16:22.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.78,0:16:25.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十号！现在我就来盯住你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.86,0:16:29.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.07,0:16:32.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 让神奈川县的第一球员
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.59,0:16:34.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧认真对应打球了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.32,0:16:40.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你几年级呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.24,0:16:43.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是高中生？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.70,0:16:45.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混…混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.18,0:16:47.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野猴子 你太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.63,0:16:49.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然找学长来助阵 你太卑鄙了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.95,0:16:51.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你白痴 你…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.17,0:16:53.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧是堂堂正正的高三学生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.95,0:16:55.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他才17岁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.39,0:16:57.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？17岁？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.23,0:17:04.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人 他怎么可能只有17岁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.96,0:17:05.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个野猴子住口
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.56,0:17:10.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛之中禁止聊天 你们两个球队集中一点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.68,0:17:11.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.28,0:17:15.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次只是警告
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.48,0:17:17.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再吵架 就禁止你们出赛了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.13,0:17:19.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心留意一点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:20.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其是双方的十号！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.19,0:17:23.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白痴是没药医的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.38,0:17:25.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.59,0:17:27.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真伤脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.07,0:17:35.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他竟然开起阿牧的玩笑来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.91,0:17:37.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是樱木嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.23,0:17:40.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知天高地厚的一年级小子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.05,0:17:42.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不怕死
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.75,0:17:48.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤木他看起来比我还老嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.58,0:17:50.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.90,0:17:57.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经你一说…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.34,0:17:58.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看我啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.60,0:18:01.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来他一直很在意…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.94,0:18:03.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 樱木
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.07,0:18:05.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 大叔 我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.45,0:18:18.34,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比赛不知道怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.20,0:18:35.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,篮板下是我的天下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.29,0:18:41.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧竟然去盯一年级的樱木
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.03,0:18:43.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 老伯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.25,0:18:45.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧 你盖的好！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.41,0:18:47.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿神
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.47,0:18:49.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.91,0:18:56.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相差六分了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.97,0:18:58.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分数拉开了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.13,0:18:59.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是海南
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.25,0:19:02.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 那个老伯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.75,0:19:04.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.97,0:19:07.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试那个看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.71,0:19:09.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有想到樱木这小子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.68,0:19:12.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面对海南的阿牧一点都不害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.81,0:19:15.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在旁边观看的我们 都为他捏一把冷汗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当初樱木才一进学校 就跟赤木学长挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.98,0:19:26.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧 您不必亲自来盯这个没礼貌的冒失家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.71,0:19:27.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来盯他就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.93,0:19:32.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来盯你已经算很抬举你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.18,0:19:34.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这只野猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.21,0:19:35.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.93,0:19:37.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十号我来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.71,0:19:48.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…？！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.45,0:19:50.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.29,0:20:03.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才看起来一点都不做作 很自然 花道！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.48,0:20:04.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良田
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.38,0:20:10.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔阳就是这个样子 受了计算之外的选手搅局
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.71,0:20:13.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才会乱了阵脚的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.06,0:20:18.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴子 我得分了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.02,0:20:21.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊！花道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.86,0:20:23.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道！假动作真漂亮…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.29,0:20:25.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱木！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.41,0:20:34.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于樱木出人意料的表现
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.14,0:20:37.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北紧紧跟住王者球队海南不放
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.36,0:20:44.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 针对状态绝佳的樱木花道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.44,0:20:48.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南的教练开始行动了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.99,0:20:56.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必需要想办法 把他弄出场才行了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.26,0:22:43.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小个子的奇怪家伙是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.63,0:22:47.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫益 去换阿神 尽可能去激怒樱木
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.13,0:22:49.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不必费力防守的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.11,0:22:53.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以被他过人的弹性 跟抢球技术给迷惑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.69,0:22:56.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他才是只有三个月经验的外行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.39,0:22:59.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭家伙！你从头到尾一动也不动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.34,0:23:00.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底想不想打球
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.27,0:23:04.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「灌篮高手」「箝制樱木的秘密兵器！」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.77,0:23:05.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要错过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散々な夢に
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目を覚ます
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日射しの強い朝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お気に入りの曲 聞きながら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗いたてのシャツ 腕をとおす
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.78,0:21:48.55,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨夜のアイツ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疲れた声だった
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺激が欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今を壊したい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.53,0:21:59.97,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おちぶれないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煌めく瞬間に捕われ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢中でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後悔する 素敵じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.20,0:22:16.18,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人じゃないし Wow
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あふれだす 涙が美しければ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人はまた 終わらぬ旅に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時を費やせるから
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}さんざん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(508.859375,620.5)\an8}ゆめ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.421875,620.5)\an8}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}ざ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(508.859375,620.5)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(566.578125,620.5)\an8}あさ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.2421875,620.5)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(490.8203125,620.5)\an8}きょく
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(526.8984375,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(303.234375,620.5)\an8}あら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(541.328125,620.5)\an8}うで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.78,0:21:48.55,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}ゆうべ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.421875,620.5)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}こえ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}げき
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(494.4296875,620.5)\an8}ほ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465.5703125,620.5)\an8}こわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(451.140625,620.5)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(364.5625,620.5)\an8}きら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(537.71875,620.5)\an8}とら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}ちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}む
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}こう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(375.3828125,620.5)\an8}かい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(498.0390625,620.5)\an8}てき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.20,0:22:16.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(373.8671875,620.5)\an8}ひとり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}なみだ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(526.8984375,620.5)\an8}うつく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(584.6171875,620.5)\an8}たび
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(378.9921875,620.5)\an8}とき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}つい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狼狈不堪的梦境里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猛然惊醒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是阳光灿烂的清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着那首喜欢的歌
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上干净的衬衫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.78,0:21:48.55,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人疲惫地对我说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要寻求刺激?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要打破现状
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.53,0:21:59.97,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再这样沉沦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕捉闪耀的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要活出我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会有后悔 也许不完美
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.20,0:22:16.18,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却已不会再孤单 Wow
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,溢出眼眶的泪水却是美丽的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又踏上无尽的旅途
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路向前 永不后退
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.41,0:11:15.01,disclaimer,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)整理修订 片源来自NGB 仅供交流学习
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.41,0:11:15.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}本集参与：Summer  Maize  曌懿  娜夏  rivercrab
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.67,0:00:35.43,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}顶着耀眼的阳光 在街上奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.59,0:00:41.89,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}你如平常一样 拍打我的肩头
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.39,0:00:48.98,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}毫无理由地迷上你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:54.32,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}你却不曾挽过我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.40,0:01:00.95,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}不知不觉 目光已被你牵引
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.20,0:01:07.29,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}不会放开 不会动摇  Crazy for you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.71,0:01:14.63,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,167)}想大声说我喜欢你 想改变世界只为你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.72,0:01:21.31,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}想劈裂冰封的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.31,0:01:28.65,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,167)}想大声说我喜欢你 踏出这一步 鼓起勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.73,0:01:36.07,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}想让你接受我这份炙热的心意
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:49.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}けん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:49.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}よせん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:49.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:49.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}すす
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.73,0:01:49.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(697.6171875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.42,0:01:52.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.46875,635)\an8}ぜんこく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.42,0:01:52.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}たいかい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.42,0:01:52.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}しゅつじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.42,0:01:52.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.6015625,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(134.8125,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.8828125,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.96875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480.0078125,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.74,0:01:56.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}たいせん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.41,0:01:58.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}おのれ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.36,0:02:07.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.3828125,635)\an8}かこ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4375,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4765625,635)\an8}れんぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.6015625,635)\an8}しゅつじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}あっとうてき
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5,635)\an8}ほこ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.5390625,635)\an8}おうじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.73,0:02:15.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.07,0:02:19.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(331.1484375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.07,0:02:19.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(381.953125,635)\an8}ひょうばん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.07,0:02:19.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}ことし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.07,0:02:19.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}たか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.3515625,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}しんしゅつ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}たお
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:22.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(727.6328125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.07,0:02:25.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.8984375,635)\an8}たいふう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.07,0:02:25.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.07,0:02:25.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}ちゅうもく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.07,0:02:25.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.046875,635)\an8}あつ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.22,0:02:43.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.22,0:02:43.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(326.5390625,635)\an8}すう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(363.3203125,635)\an8}びょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.8828125,635)\an8}かいし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.9921875,635)\an8}かんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.09375,635)\an8}ぬ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:52.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(224.859375,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:52.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}じょばん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:52.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}いっき
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:52.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}ねつ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.34,0:02:52.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0703125,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.35,0:03:09.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.44,0:03:14.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.45,0:03:16.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.73,0:03:25.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.84,0:03:28.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9296875,635)\an8}たいかい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.80,0:03:32.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(239.875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.80,0:03:32.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.0546875,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.80,0:03:32.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(690.1171875,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.01,0:03:37.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.01,0:03:37.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.57,0:03:43.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.03125,635)\an8}しんちょう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.57,0:03:43.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0546875,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.76,0:03:46.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.3984375,635)\an8}たいじゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.76,0:03:46.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.5625,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.94,0:03:50.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}みやぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.94,0:03:50.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.64,0:03:53.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}たかさご
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.65,0:03:55.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}かんたん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.65,0:03:55.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}うえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:01.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}せんしゅ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:01.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.08,0:04:01.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.47,0:04:08.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}だんな
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.81,0:04:12.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}にい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.74,0:04:14.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}そっこう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.24,0:04:19.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.24,0:04:19.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.50,0:04:25.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.3984375,635)\an8}そっこう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.50,0:04:25.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}こんど
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.50,0:04:25.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.08,0:04:29.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.08,0:04:29.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}はや
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.08,0:04:29.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}せ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.08,0:04:29.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}いきお
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.53,0:04:33.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.84375,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.53,0:04:33.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}とくい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.85,0:04:35.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.96875,635)\an8}みつい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.10,0:04:48.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}もど
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.60,0:04:51.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}あめ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.55,0:05:00.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(690.1171875,635)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.28,0:05:03.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}せんしゅ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.28,0:05:03.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.58,0:05:12.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.22,0:05:31.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.10,0:05:33.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}にたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.22,0:05:41.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.04,0:05:44.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}きよた
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.04,0:05:44.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.83,0:05:48.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.875,635)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.83,0:05:48.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}さしず
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.83,0:05:48.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}えら
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.390625,635)\an8}るかわ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}じん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.5546875,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.75,0:05:51.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.5859375,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.99,0:05:52.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}う
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.74,0:06:06.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}う
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.74,0:06:06.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.82,0:06:19.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}あま
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.82,0:06:19.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.26,0:06:23.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.40,0:06:25.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}じきでん
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.51,0:06:49.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.984375,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.99,0:07:00.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(217.3515625,635)\an8}ぬ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.99,0:07:00.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.99,0:07:00.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(772.6640625,635)\an8}なかむらくん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.31,0:07:03.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}あんぜん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.31,0:07:03.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}だいいち
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.75,0:07:08.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}ちょうし
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.75,0:07:08.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.984375,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.75,0:07:08.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.8671875,635)\an8}だいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.90625,635)\an8}ぼく
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.0859375,635)\an8}たけざと
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.02,0:07:12.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.109375,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.27,0:07:14.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(224.859375,635)\an8}しゅざい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.27,0:07:14.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(675.109375,635)\an8}あいだ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.14,0:07:16.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}はたら
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.14,0:07:16.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.99,0:07:20.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0703125,635)\an8}すく
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.33,0:07:24.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}いっぷん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.33,0:07:24.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}むだ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.52,0:07:25.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.60,0:07:33.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}きよた
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.60,0:07:33.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}のぶなが
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.25,0:07:41.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.8515625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.25,0:07:41.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}いつざい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.25,0:07:41.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.25,0:07:54.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}こしの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.16,0:08:07.34,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}せんどうくん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.80,0:08:10.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.80,0:08:10.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}たか
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.80,0:08:10.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.73,0:08:21.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.20,0:08:31.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4765625,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.20,0:08:31.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}にてん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.20,0:08:31.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5703125,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.48,0:08:32.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.48,0:08:32.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.92,0:08:34.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.26,0:08:36.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.26,0:08:36.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}あっとうてき
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.42,0:08:42.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}おとうと
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.60,0:08:44.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}ぼく
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.60,0:08:44.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}なかむら
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.37,0:08:46.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(224.859375,635)\an8}あいだ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.37,0:08:46.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}せわ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.61,0:08:49.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}ねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.10,0:08:56.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(149.8203125,635)\an8}ひこいち
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.10,0:08:56.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}がんば
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.10,0:08:56.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}はよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.10,0:08:56.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}せんどうくん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.39,0:08:59.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9375,635)\an8}はよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.39,0:08:59.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}きしゃせき
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.39,0:08:59.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.39,0:08:59.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.109375,635)\an8}おこ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.81,0:09:22.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.81,0:09:22.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}きょねん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.81,0:09:22.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}おな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.81,0:09:22.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(675.109375,635)\an8}たけざと
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.04,0:09:38.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.8984375,635)\an8}ねんかん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.04,0:09:38.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.05,0:09:54.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.05,0:09:54.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480.0078125,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.05,0:09:54.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.64,0:09:56.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}きよた
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.64,0:09:56.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0703125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.88,0:09:58.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}おお
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.02,0:10:04.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0703125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.85,0:10:06.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.32,0:10:27.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}やろう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.97,0:10:33.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(529.39453125,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.97,0:10:33.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(580.69140625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.97,0:10:33.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.80,0:10:36.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.80,0:10:36.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}きぶん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.26,0:10:39.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}ゆうめいじん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.77,0:10:41.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}めえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.77,0:10:41.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.92,0:10:53.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.47,0:11:39.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.71,0:11:42.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}いっぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.61,0:11:47.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.38,0:11:59.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}あかぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.34,0:12:06.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}あま
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.74,0:12:09.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}さる
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.14,0:12:13.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.421875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.14,0:12:13.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.453125,635)\an8}たか
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.14,0:12:13.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.578125,635)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.61,0:12:25.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}で
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.17,0:12:28.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}にい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.62,0:12:40.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.484375,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.62,0:12:40.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.69,0:12:48.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.92,0:12:53.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.92,0:12:53.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}やくめ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.92,0:12:53.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}わす
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.27,0:13:19.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.27,0:13:19.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.5234375,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.27,0:13:19.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.04,0:13:22.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.04,0:13:22.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.9765625,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.04,0:13:22.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.04,0:13:22.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.20,0:13:26.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.20,0:13:26.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}じょばん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.20,0:13:26.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}よそう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.20,0:13:26.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}はん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.20,0:13:26.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}だいけんとう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.26,0:13:32.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.875,635)\an8}しゅほう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.26,0:13:32.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}あかぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.26,0:13:32.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.984375,635)\an8}きはく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.26,0:13:32.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.99,0:13:34.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}おうじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.99,0:13:34.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.99,0:13:34.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.99,0:13:37.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.421875,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.99,0:13:37.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4453125,635)\an8}いじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.99,0:13:37.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}ゆる
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.40,0:13:42.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.5078125,635)\an8}ぜんはん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.40,0:13:42.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5625,635)\an8}ぷん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.84,0:13:50.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.6015625,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.35,0:13:54.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9375,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.35,0:13:54.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}いったん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.35,0:13:54.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}もど
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.35,0:13:54.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0703125,635)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.35,0:13:54.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.1015625,635)\an8}なお
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.28,0:14:04.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}いっぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.39,0:14:06.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.71,0:14:18.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.10,0:14:21.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(164.828125,635)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.10,0:14:21.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.10,0:14:21.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}せんりょく
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.21,0:14:22.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.38,0:14:25.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.38,0:14:25.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.38,0:14:25.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}つうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.40,0:14:56.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.33,0:15:06.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.44,0:15:17.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}あぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.87,0:15:23.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.08,0:15:24.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.20,0:15:26.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}だいじょうぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.95,0:15:34.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.95,0:15:34.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}げんき
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.86,0:15:36.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.86,0:15:38.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}だいじょうぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.86,0:15:38.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}せんせい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.02,0:15:43.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}かんとく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.91,0:15:46.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}おそ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.66,0:15:52.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}はし
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.33,0:15:58.30,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(281.5078125,635)\an8}うんどう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.33,0:15:58.30,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(333.296875,635)\an8}りょう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.33,0:15:58.30,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.83,0:16:01.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}げつ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.83,0:16:01.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.59,0:16:14.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.44,0:16:15.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.72,0:16:20.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.72,0:16:20.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}おう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.72,0:16:20.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}じつりょく
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.16,0:16:22.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}おもしろ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.78,0:16:25.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4375,635)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.78,0:16:25.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.46875,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.86,0:16:29.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.07,0:16:32.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}かながわ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.59,0:16:34.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.59,0:16:34.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.32,0:16:40.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}きみ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.32,0:16:40.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}なんねん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.24,0:16:43.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}こうこうせい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.70,0:16:45.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}やろう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.18,0:16:47.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.63,0:16:49.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.4296875,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.63,0:16:49.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(682.6171875,635)\an8}もん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.17,0:16:53.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(232.359375,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.17,0:16:53.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(682.609375,635)\an8}こう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.95,0:16:55.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}さい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.39,0:16:57.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4765625,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.23,0:17:04.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.8984375,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.23,0:17:04.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.9765625,635)\an8}さい
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.96,0:17:05.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.56,0:17:10.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}しご
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.56,0:17:10.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}りょう
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.56,0:17:10.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.875,635)\an8}ちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.56,0:17:10.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.8515625,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.56,0:17:10.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}つつし
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.28,0:17:15.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}こんかい
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.28,0:17:15.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}けいこく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.48,0:17:17.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}ぼっしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.48,0:17:17.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}つぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.48,0:17:17.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}じあい
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.13,0:17:19.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.13,0:17:19.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:20.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.4921875,635)\an8}りょうほう
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:20.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4375,635)\an8}とく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.33,0:17:20.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5625,635)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.19,0:17:23.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.19,0:17:23.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}なお
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.59,0:17:27.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}こま
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.07,0:17:35.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.91,0:17:37.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.23,0:17:40.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}こわ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.23,0:17:40.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.484375,635)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.23,0:17:40.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.05,0:17:42.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.75,0:17:48.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}あかぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.75,0:17:48.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}ほう
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.75,0:17:48.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}ふ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.58,0:17:50.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.34,0:17:58.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.60,0:18:01.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.94,0:18:03.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.94,0:18:03.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.20,0:18:35.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}した
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.20,0:18:35.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.20,0:18:35.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}せい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.29,0:18:41.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.29,0:18:41.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.29,0:18:41.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.29,0:18:41.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.25,0:18:45.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.41,0:18:47.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}じん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.47,0:18:49.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.91,0:18:56.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}ろくてん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.91,0:18:56.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.97,0:18:58.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.97,0:18:58.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}ひら
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.13,0:18:59.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.75,0:19:04.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.71,0:19:09.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.68,0:19:12.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.68,0:19:12.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.68,0:19:12.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.68,0:19:12.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.81,0:19:15.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.890625,635)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.81,0:19:15.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.81,0:19:15.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ほう
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.81,0:19:15.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}こわ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(199.21484375,635)\an8}にゅうがく
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(265.51953125,635)\an8}そうそう
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(112.296875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}あかぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}せんぱい
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.59375,635)\an8}う
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.09,0:19:21.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(727.640625,635)\an8}おとこ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.98,0:19:26.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(127.3125,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.98,0:19:26.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(217.359375,635)\an8}みずか
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.98,0:19:26.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(802.671875,635)\an8}ぶれいもの
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.71,0:19:27.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.93,0:19:32.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(164.828125,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.93,0:19:32.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.18,0:19:34.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.21,0:19:35.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.93,0:19:37.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}ばん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.71,0:19:48.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.984375,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.29,0:20:03.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.34375,635)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.29,0:20:03.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}ぜんぜん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.29,0:20:03.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.6484375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.38,0:20:10.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}けいさん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.38,0:20:10.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}がい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.38,0:20:10.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}せんしゅ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.38,0:20:10.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}まわ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.71,0:20:13.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.71,0:20:13.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}みだ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.06,0:20:18.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}はるこ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.02,0:20:21.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.29,0:20:25.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.41,0:20:34.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}よそう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.41,0:20:34.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}がい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.41,0:20:34.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}だいけんとう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.14,0:20:37.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.8984375,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.14,0:20:37.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}おうじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.14,0:20:37.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480.0078125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.14,0:20:37.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.36,0:20:44.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}ぜっこうちょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.36,0:20:44.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.36,0:20:44.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.36,0:20:44.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.44,0:20:48.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.44,0:20:48.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}かんとく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.44,0:20:48.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}たかとう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.44,0:20:48.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}うご
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.99,0:20:56.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}かれ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.99,0:20:56.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4453125,635)\an8}かや
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.99,0:20:56.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}そと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.26,0:22:43.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.26,0:22:43.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}ちい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.26,0:22:43.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}へん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.63,0:22:47.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(164.828125,635)\an8}みやます
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.63,0:22:47.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(239.8671875,635)\an8}じん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.63,0:22:47.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.90625,635)\an8}こうたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.63,0:22:47.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.63,0:22:47.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(675.109375,635)\an8}ちょうはつ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.13,0:22:49.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.11,0:22:53.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.9140625,635)\an8}りょく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.11,0:22:53.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0703125,635)\an8}まど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.69,0:22:56.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.3984375,635)\an8}かれ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.69,0:22:56.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}げつ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.69,0:22:56.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.578125,635)\an8}しろうと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.39,0:22:59.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}は
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.39,0:22:59.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.34,0:23:00.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.953125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.27,0:23:04.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(450.015625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.27,0:23:04.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0390625,635)\an8}ふう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.27,0:23:04.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.09375,635)\an8}ひみつ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.27,0:23:04.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.125,635)\an8}へいき
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.77,0:23:05.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}み