[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.9
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:诸神字幕
Original Script:诸神字幕组
Original Timing:Maize
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:960
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: CN_OP,方正准圆_GBK,37,&H00F4FBDD,&H00FBF3EF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,1,2,2,0,0,7,1
Style: JP_ED,方正准圆_GBK,33,&H00FEE8FE,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DAC5DC,&H007F7F7F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,50,1
Style: CN_ED,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00F9E1F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9E1F3,&H005F5F5F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,10,1
Style: CN,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,5,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FEF0F2,&H00FBF3EF,&H00FCF7F6,&H00FFFBFA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H00FEF0F2,&H00FBF3EF,&H00800000,&H00800000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,2,2,0,0,10,1
Style: JP,MS Gothic,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,40,128
Style: disclaimer,方正准圆_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,20,134
Style: JP-furigana,MS Gothic,14.5,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,0,0,40,128
Style: JP_ED-furigana,方正准圆_GBK,16,&H00FEE8FE,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DAC5DC,&H007F7F7F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 1,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南戦のミスの責任を取って 心機一転 丸坊主となった桜木花道
Dialogue: 1,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安西監督の指示による１年対２～３年の練習試合では
Dialogue: 1,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道の急成長ぶりに 改めて驚く赤木たちだったが
Dialogue: 1,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三井の前に 花道は次第に その弱点をさらけ出していった
Dialogue: 1,0:02:19.69,0:02:22.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,リバウンドは取れるんだ このシュートさえ入れば
Dialogue: 1,0:02:23.68,0:02:27.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうやら 彼自身にも課題は見えてきたようですね
Dialogue: 1,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崖っぷちの湘北にとって負けられない武里戦まで あと３日
Dialogue: 1,0:02:33.37,0:02:36.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道の 新たな特訓が 始まろうとしていた
Dialogue: 1,0:02:37.32,0:02:38.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木の課題は
Dialogue: 1,0:02:38.86,0:02:42.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あと３日で ゴール下のシュートが 入るようになることだ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:42.79,0:02:45.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これから３日間は寝る間もないと思え
Dialogue: 1,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:03:24.69,0:03:25.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,９３！
Dialogue: 1,0:03:29.11,0:03:29.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,９４！
Dialogue: 1,0:03:31.57,0:03:32.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,９５！
Dialogue: 1,0:03:35.00,0:03:36.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,９６！
Dialogue: 1,0:03:42.77,0:03:43.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,９７！
Dialogue: 1,0:03:45.29,0:03:46.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ストップ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:47.06,0:03:49.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,駄目だ まだ腕の力で投げようとしてるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:50.58,0:03:51.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか
Dialogue: 1,0:03:51.84,0:03:53.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ボールの持ち方は
Dialogue: 1,0:03:53.32,0:03:54.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右手を広げて こう
Dialogue: 1,0:03:55.50,0:03:56.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左手は
Dialogue: 1,0:03:57.29,0:03:58.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,添えるだけ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:58.72,0:03:59.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ
Dialogue: 1,0:03:59.92,0:04:02.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キャッチと同時に その形になってないと駄目だ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:05.81,0:04:06.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,添えるだけ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:06.81,0:04:07.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:10.11,0:04:10.94,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,添えるだけ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:11.75,0:04:12.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし いくぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:12.75,0:04:13.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう 来い
Dialogue: 1,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決勝リーグ 第２ 第３戦を前に 桜木の猛特訓が始まっていた
Dialogue: 1,0:04:21.97,0:04:24.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは ゴール下のシュートを身に着けさせ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:24.82,0:04:28.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木も湘北のオフェンスに参加させるためのものだった
Dialogue: 1,0:04:34.12,0:04:35.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ストップ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:36.36,0:04:38.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体が流れてるぞ 真上に飛ぶんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:39.16,0:04:40.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう 分かってらい
Dialogue: 1,0:04:41.07,0:04:44.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常にフォームをチェックしろ 今がいちばん大事なときなんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:44.76,0:04:47.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,間違ったフォームで練習しても うまくならん
Dialogue: 1,0:04:47.79,0:04:49.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本が大事
Dialogue: 1,0:04:50.42,0:04:51.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だろ ゴリ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:52.01,0:04:54.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのとおり とにかく反復だ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繰り返し繰り返し同じことをやって 体に覚えさせるしかない
Dialogue: 1,0:05:00.65,0:05:01.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いくぞ 桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:05:17.43,0:05:18.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,１９９！
Dialogue: 1,0:05:23.25,0:05:24.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし ラストだ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:30.29,0:05:32.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばか者 最後くらいびしっと決めろ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:33.49,0:05:34.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう一丁
Dialogue: 1,0:05:34.65,0:05:35.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,己…
Dialogue: 1,0:05:41.85,0:05:42.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２００！
Dialogue: 1,0:05:58.42,0:06:02.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見えてるんだよ 貴様のでかいずうたいは
Dialogue: 1,0:06:15.32,0:06:15.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:16.04,0:06:16.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うまいな
Dialogue: 1,0:06:16.98,0:06:18.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うまい！ うまい！
Dialogue: 1,0:06:19.43,0:06:20.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なかなか やるな
Dialogue: 1,0:06:21.77,0:06:23.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴリ！ ちょっとタイム
Dialogue: 1,0:06:27.54,0:06:29.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこで 弁当食うな
Dialogue: 1,0:06:30.13,0:06:33.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいじゃねえか 花道 減るもんじゃねえし
Dialogue: 1,0:06:34.51,0:06:37.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気が散るんだよ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:37.48,0:06:38.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おらあ！
Dialogue: 1,0:06:42.00,0:06:42.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本気だ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:44.84,0:06:45.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ったく…
Dialogue: 1,0:06:50.07,0:06:52.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気が散るっつってんだろ！ 開けんな
Dialogue: 1,0:06:55.56,0:06:58.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はがっ！ ああ… いや…
Dialogue: 1,0:06:58.85,0:07:01.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は… 晴子さんだったんですか あの… その…
Dialogue: 1,0:07:01.70,0:07:04.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいから 続けるぞ 桜木 のんびりしていたら
Dialogue: 1,0:07:04.61,0:07:05.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昼休みが終わっちまうぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:05.98,0:07:07.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お… おう！
Dialogue: 1,0:07:41.76,0:07:43.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どんどん すごくなる
Dialogue: 1,0:07:49.19,0:07:52.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の想像が 追いつかないぐらいに
Dialogue: 1,0:07:58.62,0:08:00.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ファイト！ 桜木君
Dialogue: 1,0:08:13.56,0:08:16.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし 次はミドルからのシュートだ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:26.31,0:08:27.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし 集合
Dialogue: 1,0:08:30.32,0:08:33.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あさっては武里戦だ 気合入れていけよ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:34.15,0:08:34.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解散！
Dialogue: 1,0:08:35.17,0:08:36.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お疲れさまでした
Dialogue: 1,0:09:02.64,0:09:03.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑った
Dialogue: 1,0:09:05.20,0:09:06.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと汗拭いてこい
Dialogue: 1,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,練習後の３００本は やはり相当きついか
Dialogue: 1,0:09:18.78,0:09:20.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが これでも足りん
Dialogue: 1,0:09:21.77,0:09:24.30,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間はいくらあっても 足りないくらいだ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:28.38,0:09:32.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし 珍しくあの男が文句一つ言わないな
Dialogue: 1,0:09:36.95,0:09:40.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし ラスト８８本 いくぞ ゴリ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:40.48,0:09:42.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほう まだ気合十分だな
Dialogue: 1,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然だ この気合と才能が同居する男 桜木！
Dialogue: 1,0:09:47.04,0:09:47.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ そりゃ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:49.06,0:09:49.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２１３！
Dialogue: 1,0:09:50.30,0:09:51.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２１４！
Dialogue: 1,0:09:52.74,0:09:53.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２１５！
Dialogue: 1,0:09:53.74,0:09:55.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２１６！
Dialogue: 1,0:09:55.03,0:09:55.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうした
Dialogue: 1,0:09:56.06,0:09:57.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジャンプが低くなってきたぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:59.13,0:09:59.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２１７！
Dialogue: 1,0:10:00.21,0:10:01.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指先まで神経を使え
Dialogue: 1,0:10:02.87,0:10:04.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２１８！
Dialogue: 1,0:10:09.62,0:10:11.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初心者としてバスケ部に入部して以来
Dialogue: 1,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ドリブル パス リバウンドなど地道な基礎練習を重ねてきた桜木花道
Dialogue: 1,0:10:19.23,0:10:25.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その彼にとって シュートの練習は楽しかった
Dialogue: 1,0:10:28.92,0:10:29.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイッシュ！
Dialogue: 1,0:10:31.96,0:10:32.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼鏡君
Dialogue: 1,0:10:35.43,0:10:37.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帰ったんじゃなかったのか
Dialogue: 1,0:10:37.46,0:10:41.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんな遅くに 帰ってないと うちの人心配するだろう
Dialogue: 1,0:10:43.21,0:10:44.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前はどうなんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:46.27,0:10:49.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,駅まで行ったんだけど 何となく戻ってきちゃったよ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:49.84,0:10:51.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か 手伝うことないかな
Dialogue: 1,0:10:53.24,0:10:56.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし 桜木 １段階上げるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:57.61,0:11:00.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木暮 お前がパスを出せ 俺はディフェンスだ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:02.37,0:11:03.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺は一歩も動かん
Dialogue: 1,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただ手を上げて突っ立ってるだけだ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:06.93,0:11:09.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが それだけでも結構勝手が違うぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:10.83,0:11:13.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはどうかな この天才にとっては
Dialogue: 1,0:11:14.70,0:11:16.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし いこう
Dialogue: 1,0:11:20.75,0:11:24.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,駄目だ ディフェンスを意識しすぎて 雑になってるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:36.21,0:11:38.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし！ 今のはいいぞ そのフォームだ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:40.63,0:11:42.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼鏡君はいいやつだな
Dialogue: 1,0:11:42.88,0:11:45.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺のために 親に怒られてまで
Dialogue: 1,0:11:45.78,0:11:46.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親は別に…
Dialogue: 1,0:11:48.47,0:11:51.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺は３年だから これが最後だからな
Dialogue: 1,0:11:53.15,0:11:55.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もし インターハイに行けなかったら…
Dialogue: 1,0:11:57.25,0:12:00.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あさっての陵南戦が最後の試合だ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:03.73,0:12:08.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あと３日で引退だ 悔いは残したくない
Dialogue: 1,0:12:11.89,0:12:13.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,インターハイには絶対出るぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:15.12,0:12:17.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ そうとも！ あと何本だ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:19.07,0:12:20.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ラスト３８
Dialogue: 1,0:12:20.85,0:12:22.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よっしゃ 来い
Dialogue: 1,0:13:08.66,0:13:09.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,１１８！
Dialogue: 1,0:13:12.07,0:13:13.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,１１９！
Dialogue: 1,0:13:26.38,0:13:29.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いよいよ 崖っぷちの武里戦か
Dialogue: 1,0:13:40.82,0:13:41.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,２００！
Dialogue: 1,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そろそろ 第１試合の湘北対武里戦が始まる頃だわ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:11.98,0:14:15.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絶対勝ってね お兄ちゃん 桜木君
Dialogue: 1,0:14:15.91,0:14:16.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それに…
Dialogue: 1,0:14:19.60,0:14:20.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川君
Dialogue: 1,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共に１敗してるだけに これで負けた方が先に脱落ね
Dialogue: 1,0:14:39.47,0:14:40.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうですね 相田さん
Dialogue: 1,0:14:41.74,0:14:43.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やけに気合入ってるわね 中村君
Dialogue: 1,0:14:44.35,0:14:46.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうです 油断大敵
Dialogue: 1,0:14:46.56,0:14:49.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南戦では 途中で忘れられましたからね
Dialogue: 1,0:14:50.37,0:14:53.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいか 湘北にだけは何としても勝つ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南は恐らく３戦全勝でトップを取るだろう
Dialogue: 1,0:14:57.14,0:14:58.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南戦は捨てる
Dialogue: 1,0:14:59.23,0:15:01.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うちの狙いは２位出場だ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,１勝２敗で３チームが並び 得失点差で２位を勝ち取る
Dialogue: 1,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのためには この湘北戦全勢力を出し切るつもりでいけ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:10.17,0:15:12.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,できるかぎり 点差をつけて勝つんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:12.50,0:15:13.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいな
Dialogue: 1,0:15:16.44,0:15:18.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そろそろ 時間ですね
Dialogue: 1,0:15:23.30,0:15:25.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川さん 頑張って
Dialogue: 1,0:15:26.04,0:15:26.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダンク決めろよ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:28.16,0:15:31.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ルカワ ルカワ Ｌ Ｏ Ｖ Ｅ ルカワ…
Dialogue: 1,0:15:31.13,0:15:34.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北はこの大会で すっかり人気チームになったわね
Dialogue: 1,0:15:35.50,0:15:38.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ええ 派手だし 見栄えがしますからね
Dialogue: 1,0:15:40.43,0:15:41.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それにしても…
Dialogue: 1,0:15:42.91,0:15:44.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい あいつがいないぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:44.67,0:15:46.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしたんだ 湘北は
Dialogue: 1,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南戦であの牧を吹っ飛ばして ダンク決めたやつ １０番！
Dialogue: 1,0:15:50.27,0:15:52.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤い頭の桜木がいないぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:53.18,0:15:54.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺 あいつを見に来たのに
Dialogue: 1,0:15:57.02,0:15:59.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桑田 もう１回電話してこい
Dialogue: 1,0:15:59.15,0:16:00.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,は… はい
Dialogue: 1,0:16:00.97,0:16:03.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別にいなきゃいないでいいさ その方が
Dialogue: 1,0:16:05.87,0:16:06.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始めます
Dialogue: 1,0:16:09.97,0:16:12.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのばかは一体何をやってるんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:35.45,0:16:36.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川だ！
Dialogue: 1,0:16:39.23,0:16:40.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何
Dialogue: 1,0:16:50.38,0:16:52.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北はもう赤木を下げるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:52.51,0:16:53.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温存か
Dialogue: 1,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然よ 海南戦でのあのけがが １週間で完治するわけないわ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:59.64,0:17:02.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陵南戦に備えてってことですね
Dialogue: 1,0:17:25.81,0:17:26.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強い
Dialogue: 1,0:17:29.69,0:17:33.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くそっ いつの間に湘北はこんなに強くなったんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:33.91,0:17:36.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まるっきりうちが格下のチームじゃないか
Dialogue: 1,0:17:36.99,0:17:39.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点の取り合いをしたら 武里は勝てないわ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オフェンス力なら 湘北は県内でも 一 二を争うチームよ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:52.65,0:17:54.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やはり開いたな
Dialogue: 1,0:17:57.22,0:18:00.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それにしても桜木さん 一体どないしたんやろ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:00.79,0:18:03.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの人のことだけに 気になる
Dialogue: 1,0:18:03.59,0:18:06.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 見ろ あそこ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:06.24,0:18:07.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あいつは…
Dialogue: 1,0:18:07.89,0:18:08.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何や
Dialogue: 1,0:18:11.46,0:18:12.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木だ！
Dialogue: 1,0:18:12.17,0:18:13.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何 桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:18:13.31,0:18:14.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ あの頭は
Dialogue: 1,0:18:24.19,0:18:25.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やれやれ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:28.07,0:18:29.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あと５分
Dialogue: 1,0:18:30.56,0:18:31.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ あいつ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:31.56,0:18:32.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坊主だ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:32.49,0:18:34.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いきなり坊主になってるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:34.07,0:18:35.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何考えてんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:36.47,0:18:37.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:39.87,0:18:40.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:18:43.30,0:18:45.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木さん すごい気合や
Dialogue: 1,0:18:45.42,0:18:47.68,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そっか 散髪して遅刻を…
Dialogue: 1,0:18:49.10,0:18:50.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや まさか
Dialogue: 1,0:18:53.77,0:18:55.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このばかたれが
Dialogue: 1,0:18:56.38,0:18:58.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何のために特訓したと思ってるんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:58.74,0:19:03.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや 特訓は 今朝も ２００本やって…
Dialogue: 1,0:19:05.16,0:19:08.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か ちょっと寝てたらよ そのまま…
Dialogue: 1,0:19:10.32,0:19:13.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今朝も２００本やったのか 桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:19:16.10,0:19:18.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寝るな ばか者
Dialogue: 1,0:19:18.23,0:19:20.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっとのつもりだったんだよ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:22.24,0:19:23.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日はお前は出さん
Dialogue: 1,0:19:25.03,0:19:29.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特訓の成果を わざわざ陵南に見せることはない
Dialogue: 1,0:19:31.13,0:19:32.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陵南…
Dialogue: 1,0:19:52.03,0:19:52.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あいつは…
Dialogue: 1,0:20:00.54,0:20:01.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試合終了
Dialogue: 1,0:20:01.68,0:20:02.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やった
Dialogue: 1,0:20:02.77,0:20:04.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これで１勝１敗だ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:04.35,0:20:06.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崖っぷちから １歩前進だ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:10.89,0:20:12.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだまだ これからですが
Dialogue: 1,0:20:15.45,0:20:17.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これで３敗確実だ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:17.77,0:20:20.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泣くな！ 来年また出直しだ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これで優勝争いは 海南 陵南 湘北の３チームに絞られたぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:26.25,0:20:27.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうね
Dialogue: 1,0:20:28.03,0:20:32.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして 次が 事実上の決勝戦かも
Dialogue: 1,0:20:33.45,0:20:34.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし 行くぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:36.82,0:20:37.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行くぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,崖っぷちの最初の関門 対武里戦に
Dialogue: 1,0:20:45.70,0:20:47.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木花道の出番なしでも
Dialogue: 1,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,１００点ゲームで快勝した 湘北バスケ部
Dialogue: 1,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,続く第２試合 海南対陵南の対決が
Dialogue: 1,0:20:55.84,0:20:58.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今 始まろうとしていた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:42.04,0:22:44.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仙道がじいにマンツーマンで付いた
Dialogue: 1,0:22:44.46,0:22:46.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「ボックスワン」だ 他はゾーンディフェンス
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.74,0:22:50.63,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陵南はあくまで 牧に仙道をぶつける作戦だ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.79,0:22:52.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仙道がポイントガード
Dialogue: 1,0:22:52.82,0:22:58.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいか 桜木 あの１３番をよく見てろ お前の相手になるかもしれん
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.62,0:22:59.77,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,福ちゃんが
Dialogue: 1,0:23:00.88,0:23:04.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「ＳＬＡＭＤＵＮＫ」「頂上決戦！海南ＶＳ陵南」
Dialogue: 1,0:23:05.06,0:23:06.41,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見てくれよな！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木花道為了負起海南一戰的失誤責任而剃了光頭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安西教練指示 一年級跟二、三年級分成兩隊做練習比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木花道的進步神速 使得赤木等人都驚訝不已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 在三井特意的引導下 櫻木的弱點也全部暴露出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.69,0:02:22.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搶籃板球！只要…能投進去的話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.68,0:02:27.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來他已經發現他自已的問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對於不容失敗的湘北隊 距離跟武里高中的比賽只剩三天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.37,0:02:36.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道的新特訓即將展開了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.32,0:02:38.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木在當前的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.86,0:02:42.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在未來的三日內 學會在禁區裡投球
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.79,0:02:45.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來三天你會忙得連睡覺的時間都沒有了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.74,0:02:53.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特訓三日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.69,0:03:25.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,93！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.11,0:03:29.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,94！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.57,0:03:32.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,95！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.00,0:03:36.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,96！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.77,0:03:43.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,97！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.29,0:03:46.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:49.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 你還是用手臂來投球了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.58,0:03:51.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.84,0:03:53.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿球的姿勢是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.32,0:03:54.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把右手掌張開 像這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.50,0:03:56.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那左手呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.29,0:03:58.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是輔助
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.72,0:03:59.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.92,0:04:02.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接球的時候 也必須是這種姿勢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.81,0:04:06.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是輔助
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.81,0:04:07.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.11,0:04:10.94,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是輔助
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.75,0:04:12.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 開始
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.75,0:04:13.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗷 來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進入決賽循環賽 第二場 第三場比賽之前 櫻木開始特訓了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.97,0:04:24.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是為了訓練櫻木可以在禁區內投籃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.82,0:04:28.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還可以參與湘北的反攻
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.12,0:04:35.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.36,0:04:38.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體不能夠傾斜 要往上跳！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.16,0:04:40.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗷 知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.07,0:04:44.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要常常檢討自已的姿勢 現在是非常重要的時刻
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.76,0:04:47.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以錯誤的姿勢練習 是沒有辦法把球打好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.79,0:04:49.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基礎最重要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.42,0:04:51.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不對 大猩猩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.01,0:04:54.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說得對 總之就是反復練習
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不厭其煩的重複練習 直到身體熟悉為止
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.65,0:05:01.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始吧！櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.43,0:05:18.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,199！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.25,0:05:24.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 最後一球！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.29,0:05:32.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋！最後一球更要好好的去投啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.49,0:05:34.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一球
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.65,0:05:35.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.85,0:05:42.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,200！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.42,0:06:02.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙又在睡了… 你這臭傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.32,0:06:15.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.04,0:06:16.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.98,0:06:18.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃 好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.43,0:06:20.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺能幹的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.77,0:06:23.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩 暫停一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.54,0:06:29.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准你們在旁邊吃便當
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.13,0:06:33.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼關係 花道 你又不會少一塊肉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.51,0:06:37.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們這樣會讓我分心的！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.48,0:06:38.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.00,0:06:42.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是認真的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.84,0:06:45.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:52.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說過不准開門會讓我分心！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.56,0:06:58.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會 啊啊 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.85,0:07:01.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是晴子嗎 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.70,0:07:04.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木不要在那拖拖拉拉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.61,0:07:05.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午休時間就快結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.98,0:07:07.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 嗷
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.76,0:07:43.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他越來越厲害了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.19,0:07:52.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超過我想像的程度…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.62,0:08:00.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力啊 櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.56,0:08:16.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 現在從中央投球
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.31,0:08:27.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 集合
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.32,0:08:33.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就要跟武里比賽了 大家要好好的養精蓄銳一番
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.15,0:08:34.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解散
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.17,0:08:36.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.64,0:09:03.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手滑了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.20,0:09:06.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去把汗擦乾淨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,練習後再追加三百個球 他吃不消了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.78,0:09:20.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…這個樣子還是不夠
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.77,0:09:24.30,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺時間好像再多也不夠用似的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.38,0:09:32.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過…這個小子怎麼這麼難得 一句怨言也沒有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.95,0:09:40.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 最後八十八個球了 我要上了！大猩猩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.48,0:09:42.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔 你還是這麼有精神
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那當然了 我是集精神和才能於一身的天才櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.04,0:09:47.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在胡說八道什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.06,0:09:49.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,213！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.30,0:09:51.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,214！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.74,0:09:53.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,215！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.74,0:09:55.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,216！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.03,0:09:55.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.06,0:09:57.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越跳越低了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.13,0:09:59.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,217！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.21,0:10:01.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十指記著要集中起來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.87,0:10:04.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,218！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.62,0:10:11.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是初學者櫻木花道 自從來到籃球隊以後
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次 老老實實的練習運球 傳球 搶籃板等基本動作
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:25.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對他來講…練習投籃是很愉快的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.92,0:10:29.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投得好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.96,0:10:32.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼鏡哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.43,0:10:37.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是回去了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.46,0:10:41.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼晚都不回家 家裡面的人會擔心的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.21,0:10:44.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.27,0:10:49.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是走到了車站 可是不知道怎麼搞的又走回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.84,0:10:51.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有我能幫忙的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.24,0:10:56.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 櫻木我們再更上一層樓
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:11:00.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,木暮 你負責傳球 我來阻擋他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.37,0:11:03.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不走動一步
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是把手舉起來阻擋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.93,0:11:09.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你不要以為這樣 你就可以為所欲為了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.83,0:11:13.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道會如何呢 對我這個天才而言…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.70,0:11:16.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.75,0:11:24.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！你太在乎我的阻擋了 動作變得不靈光了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.21,0:11:38.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！ 剛才那個動作實在是很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.63,0:11:42.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼鏡兄 你真夠意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.88,0:11:45.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為了我 不惜挨家人的罵…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.78,0:11:46.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這跟家人沒有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.47,0:11:51.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都已經三年級了 這是最後一次機會了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.15,0:11:55.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果沒打進高中聯賽的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.25,0:12:00.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後天對陵南的比賽 將是最後一場
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.73,0:12:08.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有三天就要引退了 我不希望留下任何遺憾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.89,0:12:13.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們絕對會參加高中聯賽的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.12,0:12:17.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 說得也是 還剩下幾球啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.07,0:12:20.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後的三十八個球
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.85,0:12:22.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 來吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.66,0:13:09.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,118！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.07,0:13:13.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,119！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.38,0:13:29.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於要跟武里破釜一戰了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.82,0:13:41.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,200！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一場比賽 湘北對武里的比賽應該差不多開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.98,0:14:15.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 你們一定要贏哦 還有櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.91,0:14:16.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.60,0:14:20.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們之前已經輸掉一場了 這場再輸掉的話就等於是提前淘汰了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.47,0:14:40.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀 相田小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.74,0:14:43.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中村 你什麼時候變的這麼投入了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.35,0:14:46.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 最忌輕敵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.56,0:14:49.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上回對海南一戰 我就是忘了這一點了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.37,0:14:53.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽清楚了沒有 無論如何 我們都要打敗湘北
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南應該會三戰全勝 得到第一名
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.14,0:14:58.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們放棄對海南一戰
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.23,0:15:01.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的目標是第二名出賽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以一勝兩敗的成績 用得失球差去決定勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此今天我們對湘北之戰 一定要全力以赴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.17,0:15:12.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要盡可能拉開分數 知道了沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.50,0:15:13.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.44,0:15:18.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間差不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.30,0:15:25.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川 加油啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.04,0:15:26.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灌個籃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.16,0:15:31.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川！流川 Love流川…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.13,0:15:34.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北在這次的大會中 似乎相當的受歡迎呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.50,0:15:38.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們表現的又傑出 而且又有看頭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.43,0:15:41.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.91,0:15:44.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎麼不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.67,0:15:46.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 湘北怎麼回事呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在對海南一戰中 甩開牧紳一 灌籃成功的那個傢伙 就是那個十號
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.27,0:15:52.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紅頭櫻木不在場啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.18,0:15:54.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是看他打球的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.02,0:15:59.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桑田 你再去打個電話去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.15,0:16:00.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.97,0:16:03.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不來就不來 那樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.87,0:16:06.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽開始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.97,0:16:12.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個大笨蛋 他在搞什麼飛機
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.45,0:16:36.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是流川！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.23,0:16:40.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.38,0:16:52.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北把赤木換下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.51,0:16:53.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保存實力嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那當然了 他在對海南之戰中所受的傷 不是一個星期就能夠治的好的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.64,0:17:02.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了保存實力對付陵南吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.81,0:17:26.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厲害…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.69,0:17:33.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 湘北隊什麼時候變得這麼強了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.91,0:17:36.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們簡直差上一大截了嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.99,0:17:39.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分數現在已經拉開 而武里是輸定了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果論攻擊實力 湘北在縣內算是數一數二的隊伍啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.65,0:17:54.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然比數拉開了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.22,0:18:00.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木 到底在幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.79,0:18:03.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是擔心他…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.59,0:18:06.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 看那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.24,0:18:07.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.89,0:18:08.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.46,0:18:12.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是櫻木！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.17,0:18:13.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽 櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.31,0:18:14.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 他頭怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.19,0:18:25.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.07,0:18:29.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還剩下五分鐘
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.56,0:18:31.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 那傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.56,0:18:32.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和尚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.49,0:18:34.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然就變和尚了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.07,0:18:35.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腦袋在想什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.47,0:18:37.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.87,0:18:40.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.30,0:18:45.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木看起來氣勢迫人！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.42,0:18:47.68,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 他是因為理發才遲到的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.10,0:18:50.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 這不太可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.77,0:18:55.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個大笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.38,0:18:58.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為我是為什麼叫你接受特訓的！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.74,0:19:03.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…我今天早上也有特訓…投了兩百個球
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:08.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投完小睡了一會 就那樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.32,0:19:13.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來櫻木花道今天早上 也練投兩百個
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.10,0:19:18.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要睡 你這個笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.23,0:19:20.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想睡一小下而已嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.24,0:19:23.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不派你上場了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.03,0:19:29.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒必要特地讓陵南…看到你接受特訓以後的成果
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.13,0:19:32.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陵南…！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.03,0:19:52.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.54,0:20:01.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽結束
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.68,0:20:02.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贏了！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.77,0:20:04.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就是一勝一負了！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.35,0:20:06.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向勝利前進一大步了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.89,0:20:12.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在才開始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.45,0:20:17.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣我們提前出局了…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.77,0:20:20.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別哭！ 明年我們可以再來挑戰嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在能夠角逐決賽權的 就只有海南、陵南跟湘北三支隊伍了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.25,0:20:27.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.03,0:20:32.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…下一場比賽或許就是實質上的冠軍爭奪戰
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.45,0:20:34.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 上場了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.82,0:20:37.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上場吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破釜沉舟的第一關卡 對武里一戰
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.70,0:20:47.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北還沒有派櫻木花道上場
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就輕鬆的獲勝拿下一百多分
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來第二場比賽 海南對抗陵南的比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.84,0:20:58.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即將開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:44.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仙道一對一盯防著牧叔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.46,0:22:46.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BOXONE 其他人都是區域聯防
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.74,0:22:50.63,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陵南是要堅持用仙道緊盯牧的策略
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.79,0:22:52.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仙道是控球後衛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.82,0:22:58.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好了 櫻木 好好看著那個13號 他或許會成為你的對手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.62,0:22:59.77,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿福
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.88,0:23:04.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「灌籃高手」 「巔峰對決 海南VS陵南」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.06,0:23:06.41,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要錯過哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:21:14.09,0:21:17.75,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,散々な夢に
Dialogue: 1,0:21:18.04,0:21:20.25,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,目を覚ます
Dialogue: 1,0:21:21.81,0:21:25.86,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,日射しの強い朝
Dialogue: 1,0:21:29.29,0:21:35.79,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,お気に入りの曲 聞きながら
Dialogue: 1,0:21:37.07,0:21:42.81,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,洗いたてのシャツ 腕をとおす
Dialogue: 1,0:21:43.95,0:21:47.02,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,昨夜のアイツ
Dialogue: 1,0:21:47.31,0:21:50.53,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,疲れた声だった
Dialogue: 1,0:21:51.01,0:21:52.86,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,刺激が欲しい
Dialogue: 1,0:21:52.92,0:21:54.77,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,今を壊したい
Dialogue: 1,0:21:54.88,0:21:58.61,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,おちぶれないで
Dialogue: 1,0:21:58.83,0:22:02.80,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,煌めく瞬間に捕われ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:02.82,0:22:05.93,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,夢中でいたい
Dialogue: 1,0:22:06.80,0:22:10.39,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,後悔する 素敵じゃない
Dialogue: 1,0:22:10.46,0:22:14.52,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,一人じゃないし Wow
Dialogue: 1,0:22:14.63,0:22:21.82,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,あふれだす 涙が美しければ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:21.93,0:22:26.06,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,人はまた 終わらぬ旅に
Dialogue: 1,0:22:26.08,0:22:30.50,JP_ED,NTP,0,0,0,,時を費やせるから
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.09,0:21:17.75,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}さんざん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.09,0:21:17.75,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(508.859375,620.5)\an8}ゆめ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.04,0:21:20.25,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.04,0:21:20.25,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.81,0:21:25.86,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.421875,620.5)\an8}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.81,0:21:25.86,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}ざ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.81,0:21:25.86,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(508.859375,620.5)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.81,0:21:25.86,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(566.578125,620.5)\an8}あさ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.29,0:21:35.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.29,0:21:35.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.2421875,620.5)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.29,0:21:35.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(490.8203125,620.5)\an8}きょく
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.29,0:21:35.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(526.8984375,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.07,0:21:42.81,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(303.234375,620.5)\an8}あら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.07,0:21:42.81,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(541.328125,620.5)\an8}うで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.95,0:21:47.02,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}ゆうべ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.31,0:21:50.53,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.421875,620.5)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.31,0:21:50.53,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}こえ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.01,0:21:52.86,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.01,0:21:52.86,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}げき
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.01,0:21:52.86,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(494.4296875,620.5)\an8}ほ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.92,0:21:54.77,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.92,0:21:54.77,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465.5703125,620.5)\an8}こわ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.83,0:22:02.80,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(364.5625,620.5)\an8}きら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.83,0:22:02.80,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(451.140625,620.5)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.83,0:22:02.80,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.83,0:22:02.80,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(537.71875,620.5)\an8}とら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.82,0:22:05.93,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}ちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.80,0:22:10.39,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}あと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.80,0:22:10.39,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(375.3828125,620.5)\an8}かい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.80,0:22:10.39,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.80,0:22:10.39,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(498.0390625,620.5)\an8}てき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.46,0:22:14.52,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(373.8671875,620.5)\an8}ひとり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.63,0:22:21.82,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}なみだ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.93,0:22:26.06,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.93,0:22:26.06,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.93,0:22:26.06,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(584.6171875,620.5)\an8}たび
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.08,0:22:30.50,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(378.9921875,620.5)\an8}とき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.08,0:22:30.50,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}つい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.82,0:22:05.93,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}む
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.63,0:22:21.82,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(526.8984375,620.5)\an8}うつく
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.09,0:21:17.75,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狼狽不堪的夢境里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.04,0:21:20.25,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猛然驚醒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.81,0:21:25.86,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是陽光燦爛的清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.29,0:21:35.79,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着那首喜欢的歌
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.07,0:21:42.81,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上乾淨的襯衫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.95,0:21:47.02,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.31,0:21:50.53,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人疲憊地對我說
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.01,0:21:52.86,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要尋求刺激?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.92,0:21:54.77,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要打破现状
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.88,0:21:58.61,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再這樣沉淪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.83,0:22:02.80,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕捉闪耀的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.82,0:22:05.93,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要活出我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.80,0:22:10.39,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許會有後悔 也許不完美
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.46,0:22:14.52,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻已不會再孤單 Wow
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.63,0:22:21.82,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,溢出眼眶的淚水卻是美麗的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.93,0:22:26.06,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又踏上无尽的旅途
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.08,0:22:30.50,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路向前 永不後退
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.28,0:12:40.14,disclaimer,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)整理修订 片源来自NGB 仅供交流学习
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.28,0:12:40.14,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}本集参与：原味  Maize  曌懿  娜夏  rivercrab
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.40,0:00:02.40,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.40,0:00:02.40,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.70,0:00:24.33,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在騷動不安中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.79,0:00:30.13,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒出的BAD NEWS
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.34,0:00:36.68,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整潔的街道的風景
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.39,0:00:44.31,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因心中的好奇而騷動
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.19,0:00:50.94,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,0)}誰也不能左右我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.36,0:00:57.11,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懷抱夢想叩響明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.37,0:01:03.12,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間流逝
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.37,0:01:10.29,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想像風一樣地生存
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.01,0:01:19.85,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Set Me Free 從永遠的長眠中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.18,0:01:26.10,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離目標還遠著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.19,0:01:32.02,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用灼熱的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.11,0:01:40.66,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追逐至筋疲力盡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.66,0:01:42.66,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(74.78125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(119.8046875,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}せきにん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9296875,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}しんき
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}いってん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.0859375,635)\an8}まるぼうず
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(825.1875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:02:02.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(885.21875,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}いちねん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(690.109375,635)\an8}れんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(149.828125,635)\an8}あんざい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.859375,635)\an8}かんとく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}しじ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}に
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0625,635)\an8}さんねん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:08.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(750.140625,635)\an8}じあい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(240.85546875,635)\an8}きゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(298.91796875,635)\an8}せいちょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}あらた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(172.3359375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}おどろ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.11,0:02:12.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}あかぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(119.8046875,635)\an8}みつい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(194.84375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.8984375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}しだい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}じゃくてん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.40,0:02:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(705.125,635)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.69,0:02:22.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.69,0:02:22.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.640625,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.68,0:02:27.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.40625,635)\an8}かれ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.68,0:02:27.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.4296875,635)\an8}じしん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.68,0:02:27.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}かだい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.68,0:02:27.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(97.296875,635)\an8}がけ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.5703125,635)\an8}たけざと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.59375,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.20,0:02:32.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(847.6953125,635)\an8}みっか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.37,0:02:36.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(224.859375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.37,0:02:36.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}あら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.37,0:02:36.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}とっくん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.37,0:02:36.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.32,0:02:38.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.32,0:02:38.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}かだい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.86,0:02:42.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(179.8359375,635)\an8}みっか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.86,0:02:42.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}した
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.86,0:02:42.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.79,0:02:45.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}みっかかん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.79,0:02:45.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}ね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.79,0:02:45.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.79,0:02:45.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(690.109375,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:49.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(232.3671875,635)\an8}だめ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:49.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.453125,635)\an8}うで
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:49.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}ちから
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:49.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.84,0:03:53.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}も
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.84,0:03:53.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}かた
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.32,0:03:54.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}みぎて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.32,0:03:54.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.484375,635)\an8}ひろ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.50,0:03:56.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}ひだりて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.29,0:03:58.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}そ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.92,0:04:02.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}どうじ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.92,0:04:02.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}かたち
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.92,0:04:02.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.640625,635)\an8}だめ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.81,0:04:06.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}そ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.11,0:04:10.94,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}そ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.75,0:04:13.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(97.2890625,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.453125,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.421875,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.5390625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.578125,635)\an8}もう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.6015625,635)\an8}とっくん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:20.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(727.640625,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.97,0:04:24.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}した
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.97,0:04:24.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.97,0:04:24.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.6015625,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.82,0:04:28.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(134.8203125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.82,0:04:28.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(224.8671875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.82,0:04:28.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}さんか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.36,0:04:38.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}からだ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.36,0:04:38.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}なが
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.36,0:04:38.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}まうえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.36,0:04:38.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.16,0:04:40.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.07,0:04:44.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(82.2890625,635)\an8}つね
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.07,0:04:44.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.07,0:04:44.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(682.609375,635)\an8}だいじ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.76,0:04:47.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.3515625,635)\an8}まちが
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.76,0:04:47.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.4921875,635)\an8}れんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.79,0:04:49.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}きほん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.79,0:04:49.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}だいじ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.01,0:04:54.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}はんぷく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}からだ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(82.2890625,635)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(142.3203125,635)\an8}かえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.3515625,635)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}かえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}おな
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.65,0:04:59.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}おぼ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.65,0:05:01.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.29,0:05:32.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.29,0:05:32.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.453125,635)\an8}さいご
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.29,0:05:32.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.49,0:05:34.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}いっちょう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.65,0:05:35.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}おのれ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.85,0:05:42.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}にひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.42,0:06:02.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(217.359375,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.42,0:06:02.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}きさま
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.54,0:06:29.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}べんとう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.54,0:06:29.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.13,0:06:33.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.13,0:06:33.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}へ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.51,0:06:37.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.51,0:06:37.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}ち
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.00,0:06:42.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}ほんき
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:52.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:52.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}ち
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.07,0:06:52.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.85,0:07:01.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}はるこ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.70,0:07:04.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}つづ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.70,0:07:04.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.61,0:07:05.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}ひるやす
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.61,0:07:05.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.19,0:07:52.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.19,0:07:52.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}そうぞう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.19,0:07:52.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.62,0:08:00.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.56,0:08:16.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.4296875,635)\an8}つぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.31,0:08:27.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}しゅうごう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.32,0:08:33.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}たけざと
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.32,0:08:33.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.32,0:08:33.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}きあい
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.32,0:08:33.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.15,0:08:34.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}かいさん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.17,0:08:36.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.64,0:09:03.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}すべ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.20,0:09:06.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}あせ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.20,0:09:06.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}ふ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(232.3671875,635)\an8}れんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}さんびゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}ご
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}さんびゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}ぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:17.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}そうとう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.78,0:09:20.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.77,0:09:24.30,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(232.3671875,635)\an8}じかん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.77,0:09:24.30,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.38,0:09:32.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.4140625,635)\an8}めずら
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.38,0:09:32.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}おとこ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.38,0:09:32.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}もんく
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.38,0:09:32.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.38,0:09:32.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.95,0:09:40.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.5078125,635)\an8}ぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.48,0:09:42.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}じゅうぶん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.48,0:09:42.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}きあい
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.09375,635)\an8}おとこ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.8515625,635)\an8}とうぜん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}きあい
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}さいのう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}どうきょ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:47.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(720.1328125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.04,0:09:47.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.06,0:09:57.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}ひく
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.21,0:10:01.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}ゆびさき
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.21,0:10:01.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}しんけい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.21,0:10:01.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.046875,635)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.62,0:10:11.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.890625,635)\an8}しょしんしゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.62,0:10:11.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}ぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.62,0:10:11.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0546875,635)\an8}にゅうぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.62,0:10:11.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(705.1171875,635)\an8}いらい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}れんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}じみち
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}きそ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(690.1171875,635)\an8}かさ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(855.203125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.36,0:10:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(915.234375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:25.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}れんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:25.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}かれ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:25.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}たの
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.96,0:10:32.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}めがねくん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.43,0:10:37.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}かえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.46,0:10:41.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(224.859375,635)\an8}おそ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.46,0:10:41.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}かえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.46,0:10:41.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.46,0:10:41.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}しんぱい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.21,0:10:44.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.27,0:10:49.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(142.3203125,635)\an8}えき
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.27,0:10:49.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(232.3671875,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.27,0:10:49.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.27,0:10:49.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}もど
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.84,0:10:51.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.84,0:10:51.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.46875,635)\an8}てつだ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.24,0:10:56.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.24,0:10:56.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.015625,635)\an8}いちだんかい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.24,0:10:56.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:11:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.8515625,635)\an8}こぐれ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:11:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:11:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.61,0:11:00.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.37,0:11:03.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.37,0:11:03.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}いっぽ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.37,0:11:03.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}うご
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}て
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.36,0:11:06.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.93,0:11:09.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}けっこう
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.93,0:11:09.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}かって
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.93,0:11:09.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}ちが
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.83,0:11:13.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}てんさい
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.75,0:11:24.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(149.8203125,635)\an8}だめ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.75,0:11:24.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}いしき
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.75,0:11:24.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.09375,635)\an8}ざつ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.21,0:11:38.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.63,0:11:42.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}めがねくん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.88,0:11:45.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.88,0:11:45.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}おや
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.88,0:11:45.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}おこ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.78,0:11:46.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}おや
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.78,0:11:46.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}べつ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.47,0:11:51.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.47,0:11:51.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}さんねん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.47,0:11:51.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}さいご
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.15,0:11:55.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.25,0:12:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(431.83984375,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.25,0:12:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(483.13671875,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.25,0:12:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}さいご
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.25,0:12:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.0859375,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.73,0:12:08.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}みっか
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.73,0:12:08.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}いんたい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.73,0:12:08.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}く
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.73,0:12:08.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}のこ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.89,0:12:13.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}ぜったい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.89,0:12:13.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0625,635)\an8}で
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.12,0:12:17.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}なんぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.85,0:12:22.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.38,0:13:29.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}がけ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.38,0:13:29.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}たけざと
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.38,0:13:29.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.82,0:13:41.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}にひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(454.35546875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(505.65234375,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.40625,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4453125,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}たけ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}さと
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:10.87,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.640625,635)\an8}ころ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.98,0:14:15.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}ぜったい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.98,0:14:15.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.9140625,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.98,0:14:15.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}にい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.98,0:14:15.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.60,0:14:20.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}るかわくん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(142.3203125,635)\an8}とも
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(217.359375,635)\an8}いっぱい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}ほう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(697.6171875,635)\an8}さき
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:38.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(772.65625,635)\an8}だつらく
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.47,0:14:40.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}あいだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.74,0:14:43.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}きあい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.74,0:14:43.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.74,0:14:43.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}なかむらくん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.35,0:14:46.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}ゆだん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.35,0:14:46.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}たいてき
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.56,0:14:49.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(232.3671875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.56,0:14:49.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.56,0:14:49.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}とちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.56,0:14:49.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}わす
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.37,0:14:53.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4453125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.37,0:14:53.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.37,0:14:53.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(682.609375,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(386.81640625,635)\an8}さんせん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(453.12109375,635)\an8}ぜんしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.859375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.8984375,635)\an8}おそ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.02,0:14:56.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.0859375,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.14,0:14:58.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.14,0:14:58.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.14,0:14:58.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.23,0:15:01.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(518.2578125,635)\an8}にい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.23,0:15:01.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(591.8203125,635)\an8}しゅつじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.23,0:15:01.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ねら
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(142.3203125,635)\an8}いっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.3515625,635)\an8}にはい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}さん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}なら
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}とくしってん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.6015625,635)\an8}にい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.640625,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:05.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(802.671875,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(377.1640625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.96875,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457,635)\an8}ぜん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(507.8046875,635)\an8}せいりょく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.94,0:15:09.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.17,0:15:12.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}てんさ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.17,0:15:12.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.44,0:15:18.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}じかん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.30,0:15:25.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}るかわ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.30,0:15:25.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}がんば
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.04,0:15:26.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.13,0:15:34.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(157.328125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.13,0:15:34.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}たいかい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.13,0:15:34.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}にんき
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.50,0:15:38.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}はで
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.50,0:15:38.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.9921875,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.50,0:15:38.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480.0078125,635)\an8}ば
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.67,0:15:46.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(104.796875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(149.8203125,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.8828125,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.9140625,635)\an8}ふ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.9453125,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.0703125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.24,0:15:50.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(810.1796875,635)\an8}じゅうばん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.27,0:15:52.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}あたま
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.27,0:15:52.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}あか
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.27,0:15:52.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.18,0:15:54.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.18,0:15:54.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.18,0:15:54.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.02,0:15:59.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}いっかい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.02,0:15:59.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}でんわ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.02,0:15:59.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}くわた
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.97,0:16:03.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(232.3671875,635)\an8}べつ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.97,0:16:03.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(697.6171875,635)\an8}ほう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.87,0:16:06.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.97,0:16:12.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}いったい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.97,0:16:12.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.45,0:16:36.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}るかわ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.23,0:16:40.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.38,0:16:52.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.38,0:16:52.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}あかぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.38,0:16:52.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.51,0:16:53.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}おんぞん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(104.796875,635)\an8}とうぜん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.859375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.8828125,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}いっしゅうかん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.0859375,635)\an8}かん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:58.91,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}ち
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.64,0:17:02.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(296.76953125,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.64,0:17:02.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(348.06640625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.64,0:17:02.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}そな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.81,0:17:26.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.69,0:17:33.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4375,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.69,0:17:33.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.69,0:17:33.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.91,0:17:36.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}かくした
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.99,0:17:39.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(217.359375,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.99,0:17:39.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.99,0:17:39.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.99,0:17:39.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}たけざと
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.99,0:17:39.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.375,635)\an8}りょく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.4921875,635)\an8}けんない
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}いち
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.59375,635)\an8}に
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.47,0:17:45.72,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(697.625,635)\an8}あらそ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.65,0:17:54.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}ひら
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.22,0:18:00.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.22,0:18:00.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}いったい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.79,0:18:03.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.79,0:18:03.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.59,0:18:06.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.89,0:18:08.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.46,0:18:12.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.17,0:18:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.17,0:18:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.31,0:18:14.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.31,0:18:14.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}あたま
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.07,0:18:29.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}ふん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.56,0:18:31.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.56,0:18:32.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}ぼうず
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.49,0:18:34.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}ぼうず
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.07,0:18:35.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(401.578125,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.07,0:18:35.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(438.359375,635)\an8}かんが
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.47,0:18:37.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.87,0:18:40.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.30,0:18:45.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.30,0:18:45.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}きあい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.42,0:18:47.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}さんぱつ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.42,0:18:47.68,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}ちこく
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.38,0:18:58.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.8828125,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.38,0:18:58.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}とっくん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.38,0:18:58.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.74,0:19:03.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}とっくん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.74,0:19:03.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}けさ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.74,0:19:03.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(548.0390625,635)\an8}にひゃっ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.74,0:19:03.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(591.5859375,635)\an8}ぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:08.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(239.8671875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.16,0:19:08.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}ね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.32,0:19:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}けさ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.32,0:19:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.9453125,635)\an8}にひゃっ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.32,0:19:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(441.4921875,635)\an8}ぽん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.32,0:19:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.6015625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.10,0:19:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}ね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.10,0:19:18.10,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}もの
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.24,0:19:23.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}きょう
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.24,0:19:23.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.24,0:19:23.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}だ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.03,0:19:29.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(187.34375,635)\an8}とっくん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.03,0:19:29.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}せいか
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.03,0:19:29.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.03,0:19:29.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.13,0:19:32.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.54,0:20:01.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(516.78125,635)\an8}しゅうりょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.54,0:20:01.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(446.84765625,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.77,0:20:04.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(476.86328125,635)\an8}いっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.77,0:20:04.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(543.16796875,635)\an8}いっぱい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.35,0:20:06.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}がけ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.35,0:20:06.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}いっぽ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.35,0:20:06.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}ぜんしん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.45,0:20:17.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さんぱい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.45,0:20:17.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}かくじつ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.77,0:20:20.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}な
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.77,0:20:20.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}らいねん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.77,0:20:20.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}でなお
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(195.82421875,635)\an8}ゆうしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(253.88671875,635)\an8}あらそ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.53125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.86,0:20:25.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.6484375,635)\an8}しぼ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.03,0:20:32.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(581.92578125,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.03,0:20:32.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(633.22265625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.03,0:20:32.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}じょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.03,0:20:32.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}つぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.03,0:20:32.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}じじつ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.45,0:20:34.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.82,0:20:37.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}がけ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}さいしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.515625,635)\an8}かんもん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(608.0625,635)\an8}たけ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.09375,635)\an8}ざと
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.36,0:20:45.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.6015625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.70,0:20:47.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.70,0:20:47.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.70,0:20:47.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}でばん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}ひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.4921875,635)\an8}かいしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}ひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.63,0:20:50.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.640625,635)\an8}ぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(514.38671875,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(565.68359375,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}つづ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.96,0:20:55.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}たいけつ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.84,0:20:58.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.84,0:20:58.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.453125,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:44.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.890625,635)\an8}せんどう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.04,0:22:44.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.0859375,635)\an8}つ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.46,0:22:46.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}ほか
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.74,0:22:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(217.359375,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.74,0:22:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.74,0:22:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}せんどう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.74,0:22:50.63,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(712.625,635)\an8}さくせん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.79,0:22:52.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}せんどう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.82,0:22:58.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(157.328125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.82,0:22:58.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.4140625,635)\an8}じゅうさんばん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.82,0:22:58.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.82,0:22:58.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5703125,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.82,0:22:58.22,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.609375,635)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.62,0:22:59.77,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ふく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.88,0:23:04.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.0859375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.88,0:23:04.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(488.2421875,635)\an8}ちょうじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.88,0:23:04.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(561.8046875,635)\an8}けっせん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.88,0:23:04.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(765.1484375,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.06,0:23:06.41,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,Default,,0,0,0,,