[Script Info]
Title:诸神字幕
Original Script:诸神字幕组
Original Timing:Maize
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:960
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: CN_OP,方正准圆_GBK,37,&H00F4FBDD,&H00FBF3EF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,1,2,2,0,0,7,1
Style: JP_ED,方正准圆_GBK,33,&H00FEE8FE,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DAC5DC,&H007F7F7F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,50,1
Style: CN_ED,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00F9E1F3,&H00FFFFFF,&H00F9E1F3,&H005F5F5F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,10,1
Style: CN,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,5,1
Style: title,方正准圆_GBK,35,&H00FEF0F2,&H00FBF3EF,&H00FCF7F6,&H00FFFBFA,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,1,2,0,0,10,1
Style: staff,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H00FEF0F2,&H00FBF3EF,&H00800000,&H00800000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,2,2,0,0,10,1
Style: JP,MS Gothic,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,0,0,40,128
Style: disclaimer,方正准圆_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,0,2,8,10,10,20,134
Style: JP-furigana,MS Gothic,14.5,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00400000,&H00400000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,0,0,40,128
Style: JP_ED-furigana,方正准圆_GBK,16,&H00FEE8FE,&H00FFFFFF,&H00DAC5DC,&H007F7F7F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 1,0:01:48.73,0:01:51.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Aブロックからの 決勝リーグ進出を懸けた
Dialogue: 1,0:01:51.27,0:01:53.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南 対 武園の一戦が始まった
Dialogue: 1,0:01:57.13,0:01:58.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全国を目指し
Dialogue: 1,0:01:58.17,0:02:00.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決勝リーグで 花道と戦うためにも
Dialogue: 1,0:02:00.74,0:02:03.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,けがを隠して出場した小田竜政は
Dialogue: 1,0:02:03.78,0:02:05.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足の痛みをこらえながら
Dialogue: 1,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懸命に 神奈川最強の王者 海南に立ち向かった
Dialogue: 1,0:02:15.59,0:02:16.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:02:16.90,0:02:18.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,100点 開こうが
Dialogue: 1,0:02:18.24,0:02:19.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,200点 開こうが関係ねえ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:20.33,0:02:21.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試合は まだ終わっちゃいねえんだ
Dialogue: 1,0:02:22.29,0:02:24.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんな かすり傷ぐれえ こうすりゃ 治る
Dialogue: 1,0:02:27.84,0:02:29.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前の言うとおりだ 桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:02:30.49,0:02:32.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試合は まだ終わっちゃいない
Dialogue: 1,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道のげきに応え 再び 闘志を燃やし
Dialogue: 1,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後の力を振り絞る小田
Dialogue: 1,0:02:41.00,0:02:44.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし 試合は 海南の圧勝に終わった
Dialogue: 1,0:02:49.75,0:02:51.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝ちたいですか
Dialogue: 1,0:02:51.06,0:02:51.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう！
Dialogue: 1,0:02:52.26,0:02:53.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よろしい
Dialogue: 1,0:02:54.05,0:02:56.23,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,友の果たせなかった夢をかなえるためにも
Dialogue: 1,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道は 自分の手で 海南を倒すことを誓った
Dialogue: 1,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして ついに 全国大会出場を 懸けた決勝リーグ第1戦
Dialogue: 1,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北 対 海南大附属の熱い戦いが始まろうとしていた
Dialogue: 1,0:03:11.29,0:03:11.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ついに
Dialogue: 1,0:03:13.70,0:03:15.45,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ついに ここまで来た
Dialogue: 1,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3年にして初めて
Dialogue: 1,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南大附属への挑戦権を手に入れたぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:03:41.37,0:03:44.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ まだ30分前だっていうのに すごい入りね
Dialogue: 1,0:03:49.12,0:03:51.96,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いくら 決勝リーグとはいえ 高校生の試合で
Dialogue: 1,0:03:51.96,0:03:54.99,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これだけ 観客が集まるのも 珍しいですね 相田さん
Dialogue: 1,0:03:56.37,0:04:00.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それだけ 両チームの注目度が 高いってことよ 中村君
Dialogue: 1,0:04:01.53,0:04:03.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まず 海南大附属
Dialogue: 1,0:04:03.59,0:04:05.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここは もう 説明不要
Dialogue: 1,0:04:05.52,0:04:06.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君でも知ってるわね
Dialogue: 1,0:04:06.95,0:04:08.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや あんまり
Dialogue: 1,0:04:08.47,0:04:09.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何 知らん!?
Dialogue: 1,0:04:09.61,0:04:11.40,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「ちゃんと勉強せい」言うたやろ！
Dialogue: 1,0:04:11.56,0:04:13.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんた 仕事なめとんちゃう
Dialogue: 1,0:04:13.65,0:04:14.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,す…すいません
Dialogue: 1,0:04:15.93,0:04:17.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く 近頃の新入社員は
Dialogue: 1,0:04:18.91,0:04:20.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見なさい あの横断幕を
Dialogue: 1,0:04:22.05,0:04:22.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「常勝」
Dialogue: 1,0:04:23.50,0:04:24.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過去16年間
Dialogue: 1,0:04:25.17,0:04:28.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南大附属はインターハイ出場を逃したことはない
Dialogue: 1,0:04:29.42,0:04:31.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「王者海南」と言われるゆえんよ
Dialogue: 1,0:04:31.93,0:04:34.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゅ…16年連続
Dialogue: 1,0:04:34.76,0:04:36.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最大のライバルといわれた
Dialogue: 1,0:04:36.62,0:04:39.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤真 率いる翔陽が破れた 今
Dialogue: 1,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,17年連続は間違いないというのが 大方の予想ね
Dialogue: 1,0:04:43.48,0:04:44.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なるほど
Dialogue: 1,0:04:44.87,0:04:46.13,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも 私は違う
Dialogue: 1,0:04:46.56,0:04:48.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波乱は まだあると思う
Dialogue: 1,0:04:50.71,0:04:52.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽を破った湘北
Dialogue: 1,0:04:59.13,0:05:02.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼らの力を 私はまだ計りかねている
Dialogue: 1,0:05:02.81,0:05:04.97,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一体 どれほどの強さを持ってるのか
Dialogue: 1,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽戦での彼らは 100％だったのか
Dialogue: 1,0:05:12.78,0:05:14.10,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,120%
Dialogue: 1,0:05:15.11,0:05:18.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも 80％に すぎなかったのか
Dialogue: 1,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僅か1点差だったという 陵南との練習試合は
Dialogue: 1,0:05:36.25,0:05:37.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波乱があるとすれば
Dialogue: 1,0:05:37.85,0:05:39.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは未知数の湘北
Dialogue: 1,0:05:40.24,0:05:41.38,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この試合よ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:42.05,0:05:43.26,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要チェックやわ
Dialogue: 1,0:05:44.33,0:05:46.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「週刊バスケットボール」記者 相田弥生
Dialogue: 1,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,実は陵南バスケ部1年 相田彦一の姉である
Dialogue: 1,0:05:58.08,0:05:59.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日の相手が翔陽でなく
Dialogue: 1,0:05:59.64,0:06:02.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北だとは 正直 驚きだな
Dialogue: 1,0:06:08.01,0:06:10.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちゃんと汗はかいたか お前ら
Dialogue: 1,0:06:22.06,0:06:24.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試合は まだですか 監督
Dialogue: 1,0:06:26.24,0:06:29.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慌てるな 牧 まだ時間はあるぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:30.15,0:06:33.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前のいいところは 勝ちに貪欲なことだ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:33.34,0:06:35.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,変に エリート面しないところだな
Dialogue: 1,0:06:36.22,0:06:37.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂上にいるお前が
Dialogue: 1,0:06:37.23,0:06:39.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いちばん 勝ちに対して ハングリーだ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:39.78,0:06:41.55,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年も お前が一番だ
Dialogue: 1,0:06:42.82,0:06:45.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さて 今日の相手の湘北だが
Dialogue: 1,0:06:46.21,0:06:47.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽が出てくると思って
Dialogue: 1,0:06:47.98,0:06:49.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何も調べとらん
Dialogue: 1,0:06:51.81,0:06:54.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結構 結構 データ 一切 必要なし
Dialogue: 1,0:06:55.36,0:06:56.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ねえ 神さん
Dialogue: 1,0:06:57.23,0:06:57.91,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう！
Dialogue: 1,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南は雲の上の存在だと思うか
Dialogue: 1,0:07:09.52,0:07:11.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手を伸ばしても 跳び上がっても
Dialogue: 1,0:07:11.62,0:07:13.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,届かない存在だと思っているか
Dialogue: 1,0:07:15.98,0:07:17.82,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,実績で言えば 確かにそうだ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:18.61,0:07:20.11,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過去の実績から言えば
Dialogue: 1,0:07:20.57,0:07:23.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南とうちは 天と地ほども違う
Dialogue: 1,0:07:23.96,0:07:25.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが 俺は
Dialogue: 1,0:07:26.54,0:07:28.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺はいつも寝る前に
Dialogue: 1,0:07:28.85,0:07:30.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この日を想像していた
Dialogue: 1,0:07:31.47,0:07:36.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北が神奈川の王者 海南大附属と
Dialogue: 1,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,インターハイ出場を懸けて戦うところを毎晩 思い描いていた
Dialogue: 1,0:07:43.91,0:07:45.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,１年のときから ずっとだ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:48.67,0:07:49.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴリ
Dialogue: 1,0:07:50.07,0:07:51.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絶対 勝つ！
Dialogue: 1,0:07:51.79,0:07:52.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう！
Dialogue: 1,0:08:02.80,0:08:05.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おーい 晴子ちゃん こっち こっち
Dialogue: 1,0:08:08.15,0:08:10.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最前列 確保しといたぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:14.97,0:08:17.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり 今回も海南の勝ちだな
Dialogue: 1,0:08:17.43,0:08:18.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相手が湘…
Dialogue: 1,0:08:19.48,0:08:21.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北の番長よ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:21.17,0:08:23.05,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おっかねえ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:26.01,0:08:28.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三っちゃん 頑張れよ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:30.76,0:08:31.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三浦台だ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:31.96,0:08:33.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,階段を2段ずつ 下りてんぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:34.90,0:08:35.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でかいな
Dialogue: 1,0:08:35.87,0:08:36.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でかい
Dialogue: 1,0:08:43.76,0:08:44.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽だよ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:50.64,0:08:51.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どれが藤真だ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:51.93,0:08:52.71,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いないよ
Dialogue: 1,0:08:59.77,0:09:01.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ 10分前よ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:01.78,0:09:02.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要チェックやわ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:41.41,0:09:42.04,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南だ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:43.36,0:09:44.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北だ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:45.11,0:09:45.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧だ
Dialogue: 1,0:09:55.21,0:09:57.56,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧
Dialogue: 1,0:10:04.70,0:10:07.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年の海南は史上最強だぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:07.88,0:10:09.57,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なぜか分かってるな
Dialogue: 1,0:10:11.93,0:10:13.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それはこのナンバー1ルーキー
Dialogue: 1,0:10:14.00,0:10:16.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清田信長が入ったからだ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:17.75,0:10:20.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ あいつは偉そうなやつだな
Dialogue: 1,0:10:20.24,0:10:22.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前なんか 見に来たんじゃねえぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:10:30.70,0:10:32.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よう 桜木花道
Dialogue: 1,0:10:32.60,0:10:34.53,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ てめぇ 偉そうに
Dialogue: 1,0:10:43.09,0:10:43.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速い
Dialogue: 1,0:10:51.22,0:10:53.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,己…
Dialogue: 1,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの2人 試合前に何をする気だ
Dialogue: 1,0:11:10.61,0:11:13.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よう 1つだけ言っとくぜ 桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:11:32.94,0:11:35.35,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すげえボールさばき 速え
Dialogue: 1,0:11:35.67,0:11:39.16,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さすが 変なやつでも 海南だけあるな
Dialogue: 1,0:11:47.37,0:11:48.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川
Dialogue: 1,0:11:49.01,0:11:50.18,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川
Dialogue: 1,0:11:59.52,0:12:00.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どあほう
Dialogue: 1,0:12:20.87,0:12:21.83,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どあほう
Dialogue: 1,0:12:21.92,0:12:22.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何!?
Dialogue: 1,0:12:23.07,0:12:25.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばか言え あほは こいつだ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:25.72,0:12:28.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや こいつこそ 明らかに あほだ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:28.53,0:12:29.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だと
Dialogue: 1,0:12:29.60,0:12:31.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「何だ？」とは 何だ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:31.89,0:12:35.69,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,な…何 これは試合前に暴力事件が
Dialogue: 1,0:12:35.91,0:12:38.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川君 駄目よ 桜木君も
Dialogue: 1,0:12:38.15,0:12:40.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面白え やれ！やれ！
Dialogue: 1,0:12:40.16,0:12:42.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助っとが必要なら いつでも言ってくれよ 花道
Dialogue: 1,0:12:46.43,0:12:50.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいか 桜木 1つだけ言っとくぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:53.28,0:12:55.92,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナンバー1ルーキーは こいつじゃねえ
Dialogue: 1,0:12:57.74,0:12:59.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当たり前だ
Dialogue: 1,0:13:13.23,0:13:13.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速え
Dialogue: 1,0:13:44.13,0:13:45.22,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すげえ
Dialogue: 1,0:13:45.52,0:13:47.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北も負けてねえぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:13:47.08,0:13:49.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいぞ いいぞ 湘北
Dialogue: 1,0:13:50.12,0:13:52.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頑張って 花道さん
Dialogue: 1,0:13:52.75,0:13:54.59,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すてきよ 花ちゃん
Dialogue: 1,0:13:57.70,0:13:59.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一体 何 考えてんのか
Dialogue: 1,0:14:09.25,0:14:11.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナンバー1は 流川じゃねえ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:11.47,0:14:14.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほほう 全く そのとおり
Dialogue: 1,0:14:16.30,0:14:18.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,てめぇにゃ負けねえぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:14:59.07,0:15:01.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ホントに 高校生なんですか あの2人
Dialogue: 1,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南と湘北の大きな共通点を見つけたわ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:08.39,0:15:09.39,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧と赤木
Dialogue: 1,0:15:10.32,0:15:13.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,両チームとも 揺るぎない強力な大黒柱がいる
Dialogue: 1,0:15:16.84,0:15:19.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも あの2人の歩いてきた道は
Dialogue: 1,0:15:19.21,0:15:20.66,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,実に対照的ね
Dialogue: 1,0:15:23.29,0:15:26.25,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人は 1年のときから「怪物」と呼ばれ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:26.57,0:15:28.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常にトップを走り続けてきた男
Dialogue: 1,0:15:30.40,0:15:33.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして もう一人は ものすごい素質を持ち
Dialogue: 1,0:15:33.77,0:15:36.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,実力的には 県内屈指のプレーヤーでありながら
Dialogue: 1,0:15:37.04,0:15:40.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,チームメートに恵まれず 埋もれ続けてきた男
Dialogue: 1,0:15:42.62,0:15:44.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すまん 失礼をした
Dialogue: 1,0:15:45.48,0:15:47.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや こっちこそ
Dialogue: 1,0:15:51.24,0:15:52.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この ばかが
Dialogue: 1,0:15:53.28,0:15:54.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばか野郎
Dialogue: 1,0:15:54.47,0:15:55.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北の恥
Dialogue: 1,0:15:56.58,0:15:59.67,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く 何 考えてんだ お前は
Dialogue: 1,0:16:00.97,0:16:02.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木君
Dialogue: 1,0:16:03.75,0:16:06.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君 バスケは いつから始めたんだね
Dialogue: 1,0:16:11.24,0:16:12.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だ じじい
Dialogue: 1,0:16:12.64,0:16:13.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高校からだよ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:14.08,0:16:15.47,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なめんじゃねえよ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:15.80,0:16:16.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばかたれ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:17.57,0:16:19.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口の利き方に注意せんか！
Dialogue: 1,0:16:20.18,0:16:21.50,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高校から
Dialogue: 1,0:16:22.27,0:16:25.48,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,い…痛…い…
Dialogue: 1,0:16:26.23,0:16:28.19,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ3か月足らずか
Dialogue: 1,0:16:35.18,0:16:38.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして 高校最後の今年
Dialogue: 1,0:16:39.93,0:16:43.07,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤木君も とうとう ここまで来た
Dialogue: 1,0:16:48.08,0:16:49.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ 始まりますよ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:53.15,0:16:54.32,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし いこうぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:16:54.67,0:16:55.46,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう！
Dialogue: 1,0:16:57.26,0:16:59.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごいチームメートたちを得て
Dialogue: 1,0:17:02.77,0:17:03.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いくぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:03.91,0:17:04.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おう！
Dialogue: 1,0:17:17.77,0:17:22.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フレフレ 海南 フレフレ 海南 フレフレ 海南
Dialogue: 1,0:17:22.80,0:17:24.15,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レッツゴー ルカワ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:24.25,0:17:28.02,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,スペシャル ルカワ デリシャス ルカワ
Dialogue: 1,0:17:33.71,0:17:34.51,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始めます
Dialogue: 1,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北！湘北！湘北…
Dialogue: 1,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南！海南！海南…
Dialogue: 1,0:18:09.08,0:18:10.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見てたぜ 翔陽戦
Dialogue: 1,0:18:10.95,0:18:13.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダンク 決める気分ってのは どんなだ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:15.13,0:18:16.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さすが有名人
Dialogue: 1,0:18:18.09,0:18:19.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前には分かるまい
Dialogue: 1,0:18:30.04,0:18:30.44,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし
Dialogue: 1,0:18:34.07,0:18:35.03,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すげえパス
Dialogue: 1,0:18:35.16,0:18:35.76,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし
Dialogue: 1,0:18:36.50,0:18:37.54,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狙いどおり
Dialogue: 1,0:18:42.02,0:18:43.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何やの すごいジャンプ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:44.04,0:18:44.86,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダンクだ
Dialogue: 1,0:18:49.49,0:18:50.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧！
Dialogue: 1,0:18:50.48,0:18:52.73,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おおっ さすが牧さん やった
Dialogue: 1,0:18:55.95,0:18:56.84,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うまい
Dialogue: 1,0:18:58.89,0:18:59.33,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし
Dialogue: 1,0:19:00.30,0:19:00.79,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神
Dialogue: 1,0:19:03.55,0:19:05.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よっしゃ 神さん パス
Dialogue: 1,0:19:07.77,0:19:08.42,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信長
Dialogue: 1,0:19:09.51,0:19:11.12,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こら！待て 猿
Dialogue: 1,0:19:11.30,0:19:12.58,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰が猿だと
Dialogue: 1,0:19:12.60,0:19:13.52,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待て 野猿
Dialogue: 1,0:19:13.64,0:19:15.27,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猿はてめぇだ 赤毛猿
Dialogue: 1,0:19:15.46,0:19:16.28,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木
Dialogue: 1,0:19:19.20,0:19:19.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何!?
Dialogue: 1,0:19:20.94,0:19:22.81,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高い
Dialogue: 1,0:19:25.06,0:19:25.75,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桜木君
Dialogue: 1,0:19:25.77,0:19:28.08,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし 花道 いいぞ いいぞ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:32.99,0:19:33.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歩いた
Dialogue: 1,0:19:36.80,0:19:37.70,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トラベリング
Dialogue: 1,0:19:40.24,0:19:43.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（DR.T）「トラベリング」ボールを持って 3歩 歩いてはいけません
Dialogue: 1,0:19:44.52,0:19:46.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初歩です 初歩 初歩です
Dialogue: 1,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.85,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,てめぇのぼけのおかげで 助かったぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:19:53.97,0:19:55.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野猿
Dialogue: 1,0:20:01.80,0:20:02.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ナイスカットだ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:05.24,0:20:06.93,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か すげえぜ この試合
Dialogue: 1,0:20:07.40,0:20:09.17,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ 海南も すごいが
Dialogue: 1,0:20:09.29,0:20:11.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北も 何か ものすごいじゃんか
Dialogue: 1,0:20:12.08,0:20:15.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽に勝ったのも これなら うなずけるぜ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:17.15,0:20:18.20,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何て子たちなの
Dialogue: 1,0:20:18.84,0:20:19.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始 数秒で
Dialogue: 1,0:20:19.94,0:20:21.65,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,観衆のどぎもを抜いた
Dialogue: 1,0:20:22.12,0:20:24.89,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴリ 気合 入りまくってるな
Dialogue: 1,0:20:24.90,0:20:25.78,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当たり前だ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:26.22,0:20:27.60,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前は入っていないのか
Dialogue: 1,0:20:30.17,0:20:31.90,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この天才に愚問を
Dialogue: 1,0:20:32.37,0:20:35.24,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 気合 入りまくりよ
Dialogue: 1,0:20:38.61,0:20:41.29,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ついに 注目の決勝リーグ第1戦
Dialogue: 1,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北 対 海南大附属の試合が始まった
Dialogue: 1,0:20:47.16,0:20:48.80,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして 両校の選手たちは
Dialogue: 1,0:20:48.91,0:20:51.37,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始早々から スーパープレーを連発
Dialogue: 1,0:20:51.74,0:20:53.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,たちまち 大観衆の目を奪った
Dialogue: 1,0:20:55.50,0:20:59.36,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まさに 波乱の幕開けと呼ぶに ふさわしいスタートを
Dialogue: 1,0:20:59.51,0:21:01.09,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切ったのだった
Dialogue: 1,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 1,0:22:41.46,0:22:43.61,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見よ リバウンド王の実力
Dialogue: 1,0:22:43.72,0:22:44.74,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい 野猿
Dialogue: 1,0:22:44.83,0:22:47.49,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この桜木をこけにしやがると どうなるか思い知ったか
Dialogue: 1,0:22:47.85,0:22:48.88,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いくぞ 速攻
Dialogue: 1,0:22:49.22,0:22:50.43,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じい 勝負だ
Dialogue: 1,0:22:50.50,0:22:51.64,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ばかか てめぇは
Dialogue: 1,0:22:51.76,0:22:55.01,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牧さんが お前みたいな 無礼者を相手にすると思うか
Dialogue: 1,0:22:55.09,0:22:56.31,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほざけ 野猿
Dialogue: 1,0:22:56.58,0:22:57.98,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神奈川ナンバー1プレーヤーは
Dialogue: 1,0:22:58.04,0:22:59.14,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この俺が倒す
Dialogue: 1,0:22:59.58,0:23:03.21,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「SLAMDUNK」「計算外!?花道絶好調！」
Dialogue: 1,0:23:03.38,0:23:04.62,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見てくれよな！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.73,0:01:51.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,A組爭取決賽權的關鍵一戰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.27,0:01:53.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南附中對抗武園高中的比賽開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:01:58.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小田龍政為了稱霸全國
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.17,0:02:00.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在決賽中 跟櫻木一分勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.74,0:02:03.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而隱瞞自已的傷勢勉強上場
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.78,0:02:05.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他強忍著腳傷的痛楚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拚命的跟神奈川縣 最強的球隊海南對抗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.59,0:02:16.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.90,0:02:18.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他輸掉100分
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.24,0:02:19.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是200分 這都沒有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.33,0:02:21.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之比賽還沒有結束呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.29,0:02:24.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這點小傷我只要這麼做就會好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.84,0:02:29.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木 你說的一點都沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:32.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽還沒有結束呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受到櫻木花道的激勵 小田重新燃起鬥志
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使出了僅存的最後力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:44.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 比賽還是以海南的壓倒性勝利收場
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.75,0:02:51.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們想贏嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.06,0:02:51.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.26,0:02:53.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.05,0:02:56.23,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了實現朋友 無法達成的夢想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木發誓要靠自已的力量 來打倒海南大附屬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爭取參加全國大賽機會的決賽第一場戰役
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北對抗海南大附屬的激烈比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.29,0:03:11.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.70,0:03:15.45,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於打到這裡來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三年來第一次讓我…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到了 向海南大附屬挑戰的權利
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.89,0:03:28.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向王者挑戰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.37,0:03:44.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在才是比賽前三十分鐘 觀眾就湧進來這麼多了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.12,0:03:51.96,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說是決賽 但只是高中生比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.96,0:03:54.99,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能夠吸引這麼多的觀眾 實在是非常罕見 相田小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:04:00.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中村 由此可以證實 這兩隊受到注目的程度到底有多高了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:03.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先我們來看海南大附屬
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.59,0:04:05.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們不需要我說明
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.52,0:04:06.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該已經相當瞭解了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.95,0:04:08.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…我不是很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.47,0:04:09.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？你不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.61,0:04:11.40,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是叫你先研究一下的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.56,0:04:13.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是看不起我們這份工作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.65,0:04:14.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對…對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.93,0:04:17.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了最近的新職員
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.91,0:04:20.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 你仔細看一下那邊的布條
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.05,0:04:22.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「常勝」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.50,0:04:24.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在過去十六年裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.17,0:04:28.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南大附屬連續打進高中聯賽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.42,0:04:31.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個就是海南被稱為王者的由來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.93,0:04:34.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連…連贏十六年
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.76,0:04:36.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤真所率領的翔陽一直被認為是他們最大的勁敵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.62,0:04:39.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是現在翔陽被淘汰了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此普遍認為海南這次連贏十七年也沒問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.48,0:04:44.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.87,0:04:46.13,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不這麼認為
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.56,0:04:48.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次可能還有變數存在
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.71,0:04:52.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是打敗翔陽的湘北
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.13,0:05:02.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我目前都無法預估他們的實力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.81,0:05:04.97,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們到底擁有多強的實力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在與翔陽的比賽中他們到底是發揮了百分之百的實力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.78,0:05:14.10,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是百分之一百二十
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.11,0:05:18.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者…他們只發揮了百分之八十的實力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有那次跟陵南交手 比數只差一分的練習比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.25,0:05:37.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果說比賽會再生變數
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.85,0:05:39.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼一定是未知數的湘北
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.24,0:05:41.38,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.05,0:05:43.26,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一定要好好的觀察才行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.33,0:05:46.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位籃球週刊的記者 相田彌生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就是陵南籃球隊一年級相田彥一的姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.08,0:05:59.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是嚇了一大跳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.64,0:06:02.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不到今天的對手 不是翔陽而是湘北
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.01,0:06:10.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 你們都已經做好熱身運動了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.06,0:06:24.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽還沒有開始嗎？教練
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.24,0:06:29.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要著急 阿牧 還有一段時間呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.15,0:06:33.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的優點就是渴望得到勝利的貪念
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.34,0:06:35.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和絕不輕敵的態度
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.22,0:06:37.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體能處於顛峰的你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.23,0:06:39.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對勝利的饑渴也達到頂點
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.78,0:06:41.55,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年你也是最強的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.82,0:06:45.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於今天的對手湘北籃球隊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.21,0:06:47.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我沒有想到他會打敗翔陽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.98,0:06:49.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就沒有調查他們
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.81,0:06:54.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 很好 反正本來就不需要什麼資料
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.36,0:06:56.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不對啊 阿神
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.23,0:06:57.91,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們認為海南是遠在雲端之上 遙不可及的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.52,0:07:11.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們認為他們的實力
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.62,0:07:13.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們跳起來也夠不到的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.98,0:07:17.82,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以實際成績來說這個是沒錯的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.61,0:07:20.11,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以過去實際成績來看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.57,0:07:23.00,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們跟海南大附屬的差距就像天跟地一樣的遠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.96,0:07:25.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.54,0:07:28.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在每一天睡覺以前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.85,0:07:30.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不停的想象這一天的來臨
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:36.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想象我們湘北跟神奈川縣的王者
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南大附屬爭奪高中聯賽參賽權的一戰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.91,0:07:45.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從一年級就開始每天這樣想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.67,0:07:49.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.07,0:07:51.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要贏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.79,0:07:52.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.80,0:08:05.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴子 我幫你佔一個好位子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.15,0:08:10.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快來 在最前面
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.97,0:08:17.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一次一定是海南勝利
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.43,0:08:18.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對手是湘…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.48,0:08:21.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北的不良少年
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.17,0:08:23.05,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.01,0:08:28.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小三 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.76,0:08:31.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三浦台
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.96,0:08:33.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們一次跨兩格樓梯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.90,0:08:35.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好壯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.87,0:08:36.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.76,0:08:44.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔陽的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.64,0:08:51.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪個是藤真呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.93,0:08:52.71,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不曉得
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.77,0:09:01.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還差十分鐘了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.78,0:09:02.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得好好的觀察
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.41,0:09:42.04,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.36,0:09:44.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是湘北…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.11,0:09:45.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是阿牧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.21,0:09:57.56,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.70,0:10:07.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年的海南是歷史上最強的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.88,0:10:09.57,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們知道什麼原因嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.93,0:10:13.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是因為海南有我清田信長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.00,0:10:16.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個超級新星加入的關係
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.75,0:10:20.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是誰呀？怎麼那麼自大
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.24,0:10:22.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可不是專程來看你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.70,0:10:32.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木花道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.60,0:10:34.53,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在得意什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.09,0:10:43.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.22,0:10:53.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那兩個人 比賽還沒有開始 他們想幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.61,0:11:13.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木 我先露一點給你瞧瞧好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.94,0:11:35.35,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害…這麼純熟的運球動作
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.67,0:11:39.16,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不到海南也有這麼厲害的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.37,0:11:48.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川楓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.01,0:11:50.18,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川楓
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.52,0:12:00.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.87,0:12:21.83,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.92,0:12:22.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.07,0:12:25.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡說八道 笨蛋應該是這個傢伙才對
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.72,0:12:28.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對 笨蛋很明顯 是你這個傢伙才對
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.53,0:12:29.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.60,0:12:31.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是要這麼說 你想怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.89,0:12:35.69,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼搞的 比賽都還沒有開始 就鬧出暴力事件
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.91,0:12:38.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流川楓 櫻木 這樣不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.15,0:12:40.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太有意思了 打 打
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.16,0:12:42.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果需要人幫忙的話 隨時可以找我們 櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.43,0:12:50.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木 你給我聽好了 我先聲明一件事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.28,0:12:55.92,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最超級的新星 絕對不是這個傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.74,0:12:59.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你講廢話嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.23,0:13:13.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.13,0:13:45.22,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.52,0:13:47.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北好像不會輸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.08,0:13:49.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯啊 湘北
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.12,0:13:52.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊花道！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.75,0:13:54.59,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小花太帥了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.70,0:13:59.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他到底在想什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.25,0:14:11.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最超級的新人不是流川楓
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.47,0:14:14.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一點說得沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.30,0:14:18.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是絕對不會輸給你的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.07,0:15:01.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看那倆個人 他們真的是高中生嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到海南跟湘北 兩個大的共通點了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.39,0:15:09.39,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧跟赤木
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.32,0:15:13.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩支球隊都有不可動搖的兩大支柱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.84,0:15:19.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…他們倆個人走過來的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.21,0:15:20.66,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻是截然相反的兩條路
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.29,0:15:26.25,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一條是從一年級的時候開始 就被稱為怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:28.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直走在頂點的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.40,0:15:33.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而另一條 擁有驚人的籃球天份
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.77,0:15:36.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,論實力是縣內屈指可數的好球員
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.04,0:15:40.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻因為沒有與其合作的隊友 而一直遭到埋沒的孤獨男人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.62,0:15:44.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 他們太沒禮貌了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.48,0:15:47.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡 我們才是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.24,0:15:52.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.28,0:15:54.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.47,0:15:55.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北的羞恥嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.58,0:15:59.67,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的腦筋到底在想什麼東西 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.97,0:16:02.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.75,0:16:06.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是從什麼時候 開始打籃球的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.24,0:16:12.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹什麼 老頭子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.64,0:16:13.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從高中開始打籃球的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.08,0:16:15.47,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 看不起我是不是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.80,0:16:16.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.57,0:16:19.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你講話不會注重禮貌一些嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.18,0:16:21.50,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中才開始打籃球
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.27,0:16:25.48,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.23,0:16:28.19,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不滿三個月呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.18,0:16:38.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年是高中的最後一年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.93,0:16:43.07,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤木他終於打到這個地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.08,0:16:49.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 要開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.15,0:16:54.32,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 我們要上場了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.67,0:16:55.46,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.26,0:16:59.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他得到好的隊友了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.77,0:17:03.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上場吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.91,0:17:04.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.77,0:17:22.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 海南 加油 海南
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.80,0:17:24.15,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 加油…流川楓
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.25,0:17:28.02,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 加油…流川楓
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.71,0:17:34.51,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽開始
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北！湘北！湘北…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海南！海南！海南…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.08,0:18:10.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們跟翔陽的比賽我看過了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.95,0:18:13.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灌籃成功的心情怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.13,0:18:16.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我果然是個名人了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.09,0:18:19.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你絕對不會知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.04,0:18:30.44,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.07,0:18:35.03,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傳得太漂亮了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.16,0:18:35.76,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.50,0:18:37.54,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟計劃的一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.02,0:18:43.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是嚇死人了 跳這麼高呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.04,0:18:44.86,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灌籃了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.49,0:18:50.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿牧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.48,0:18:52.73,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 不愧是我們的阿牧 幹得好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.95,0:18:56.84,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.89,0:18:59.33,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.30,0:19:00.79,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿神
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.55,0:19:05.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿神 這邊 快點
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.77,0:19:08.42,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信長
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.51,0:19:11.12,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 別跑 你這個小猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.30,0:19:12.58,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說誰是小猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.60,0:19:13.52,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.64,0:19:15.27,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是猴子 紅頭猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.46,0:19:16.28,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.20,0:19:19.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.94,0:19:22.81,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好誇張哦 好高
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.06,0:19:25.75,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻木
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.77,0:19:28.08,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花道 好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.99,0:19:33.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他走步了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.80,0:19:37.70,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶球走步
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.24,0:19:43.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶球走步指拿到籃球之後 不可以走超過三步
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.52,0:19:46.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是基本常識 基本常識
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.85,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧你這只白癡 得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.97,0:19:55.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這只野猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.80,0:20:02.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,截得好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.24,0:20:06.93,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場比賽勝負很難預測
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.40,0:20:09.17,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 海南很厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.29,0:20:11.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是湘北似乎比海南更厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.08,0:20:15.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得他們能夠打贏翔陽 原來是這麼強
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.15,0:20:18.20,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些孩子太厲害了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.84,0:20:19.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽開始還沒幾秒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.94,0:20:21.65,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就讓觀眾看得目瞪口呆的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.12,0:20:24.89,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大猩猩 你現在鬥志滿滿了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.90,0:20:25.78,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.22,0:20:27.60,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是你沒有自信
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.17,0:20:31.90,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別對本天才問笨問題
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.37,0:20:35.24,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我當然…鬥志滿滿了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.61,0:20:41.29,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬眾矚目的第一戰
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,湘北對海南大附屬的比賽 終於開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.16,0:20:48.80,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩所學校的選手們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.91,0:20:51.37,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比賽一開始 就演出了超級精彩的爭奪戰
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.74,0:20:53.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上吸引全場觀眾的視線
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.50,0:20:59.36,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個開場為不久以後
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.51,0:21:01.09,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉開了龍爭虎鬥的序幕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.46,0:22:43.61,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我籃板王的實力
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.72,0:22:44.74,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 野猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.83,0:22:47.49,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小看我櫻木的話 知道會有什麼後果嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.85,0:22:48.88,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 速攻
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.22,0:22:50.43,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決一勝負了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.50,0:22:51.64,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.76,0:22:55.01,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以為阿牧會把你這樣沒禮貌的冒失鬼當對手嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.09,0:22:56.31,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少胡說 野猴子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.58,0:22:57.98,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神奈川第一的球員
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.04,0:22:59.14,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來打倒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.58,0:23:03.21,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「灌籃高手」「計算之外？！花道狀態一流！」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.38,0:23:04.62,CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要錯過啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散々な夢に
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目を覚ます
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日射しの強い朝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お気に入りの曲 聞きながら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗いたてのシャツ 腕をとおす
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.78,0:21:48.55,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨夜のアイツ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疲れた声だった
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺激が欲しい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今を壊したい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.53,0:21:59.97,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おちぶれないで
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煌めく瞬間に捕われ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢中でいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後悔する 素敵じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.20,0:22:16.18,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一人じゃないし Wow
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あふれだす 涙が美しければ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人はまた 終わらぬ旅に
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,JP_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時を費やせるから
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}さんざん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(508.859375,620.5)\an8}ゆめ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.421875,620.5)\an8}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}ざ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(508.859375,620.5)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(566.578125,620.5)\an8}あさ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.2421875,620.5)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(490.8203125,620.5)\an8}きょく
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(526.8984375,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(303.234375,620.5)\an8}あら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(541.328125,620.5)\an8}うで
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.78,0:21:48.55,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(422.28125,620.5)\an8}ゆうべ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(393.421875,620.5)\an8}つか
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}こえ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}げき
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(494.4296875,620.5)\an8}ほ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465.5703125,620.5)\an8}こわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(451.140625,620.5)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,620.5)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(364.5625,620.5)\an8}きら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(537.71875,620.5)\an8}とら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}ちゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(407.8515625,620.5)\an8}む
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}こう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(375.3828125,620.5)\an8}かい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}す
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(498.0390625,620.5)\an8}てき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.20,0:22:16.18,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(373.8671875,620.5)\an8}ひとり
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}なみだ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(526.8984375,620.5)\an8}うつく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(346.5234375,620.5)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(469.1796875,620.5)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(584.6171875,620.5)\an8}たび
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(378.9921875,620.5)\an8}とき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,JP_ED-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(436.7109375,620.5)\an8}つい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.27,0:21:18.90,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狼狽不堪的夢境里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.63,0:21:21.79,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猛然驚醒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:27.18,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是陽光燦爛的清晨
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:37.11,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着那首喜欢的歌
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.83,0:21:44.50,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上乾淨的襯衫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.78,0:21:48.55,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.91,0:21:52.37,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人疲憊地對我說
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.71,0:21:54.49,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要尋求刺激?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.68,0:21:56.35,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要打破现状
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.53,0:21:59.97,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再這樣沉淪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.30,0:22:04.30,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捕捉闪耀的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.38,0:22:07.48,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要活出我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.41,0:22:11.98,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許會有後悔 也許不完美
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.20,0:22:16.18,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻已不會再孤單 Wow
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.36,0:22:23.33,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,溢出眼眶的淚水卻是美麗的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.67,0:22:27.30,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又踏上无尽的旅途
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.54,0:22:31.60,CN_ED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路向前 永不後退
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.27,0:12:16.89,disclaimer,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)整理修订 片源来自NGB 仅供交流学习
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.27,0:12:16.89,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}本集参与：Summer  Maize  曌懿  娜夏  rivercrab
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.67,0:00:35.43,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}頂著耀眼的陽光 在街上奔跑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.59,0:00:41.89,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}你如平常一樣 拍打我的肩頭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.39,0:00:48.98,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}毫無理由地迷上你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:54.32,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}你卻不曾挽過我的手
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.40,0:01:00.95,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}不知不覺 目光已被你牽引
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.20,0:01:07.29,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}不會放開 不會動搖  Crazy for you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.71,0:01:14.63,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,167)}想大聲說我喜歡你 想改變世界只為你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.72,0:01:21.31,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}想劈裂冰封的時間
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.31,0:01:28.65,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,167)}想大聲說我喜歡你 踏出這一步 鼓起勇氣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.73,0:01:36.07,CN_OP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(167,167)}想讓你接受我這份炙熱的心意
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.73,0:01:51.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.73,0:01:51.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}しんしゅつ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.73,0:01:51.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(690.1171875,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.27,0:01:53.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.9765625,635)\an8}たけぞの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.27,0:01:53.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.8984375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.27,0:01:53.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.27,0:01:53.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}いっせん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.27,0:01:53.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:01:58.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ぜんこく
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:01:58.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:01:58.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}ざ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.17,0:02:00.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.17,0:02:00.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}たたか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.17,0:02:00.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.74,0:02:03.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}かく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.74,0:02:03.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}しゅつじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.74,0:02:03.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0546875,635)\an8}おだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.74,0:02:03.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.0859375,635)\an8}たつまさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.78,0:02:05.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}あし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.78,0:02:05.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}さいきょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(194.84375,635)\an8}けんめい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}かながわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}おうじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.0859375,635)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.25,0:02:09.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(690.1171875,635)\an8}む
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.59,0:02:16.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.90,0:02:18.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}ひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.90,0:02:18.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.984375,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.90,0:02:18.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480.015625,635)\an8}ひら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.24,0:02:19.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}にひゃくてん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.24,0:02:19.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.984375,635)\an8}ひら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.24,0:02:19.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0546875,635)\an8}かんけい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.33,0:02:21.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.33,0:02:21.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.29,0:02:24.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}きず
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.29,0:02:24.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(712.6328125,635)\an8}なお
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.84,0:02:29.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.84,0:02:29.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.84,0:02:29.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:32.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.40625,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.49,0:02:32.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.875,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.9609375,635)\an8}こた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}ふたた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}とうし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}も
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}さいご
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ちから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}ふ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}しぼ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.0703125,635)\an8}おだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:44.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:44.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:44.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}あっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:44.44,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.0859375,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.75,0:02:51.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.05,0:02:56.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.859375,635)\an8}とも
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.05,0:02:56.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.890625,635)\an8}は
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.05,0:02:56.23,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}ゆめ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.8515625,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}じぶん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}て
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480.0078125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}たお
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.53,0:02:59.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(705.125,635)\an8}ちか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(368.1796875,635)\an8}ぜんこくたいかい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(471.7578125,635)\an8}しゅつじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(795.171875,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.25,0:03:04.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(840.203125,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.015625,635)\an8}たたか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(149.8203125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.859375,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(269.8984375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9375,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.984375,635)\an8}あつ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:09.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.70,0:03:15.45,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(461.85546875,635)\an8}ちょうせん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(513.15234375,635)\an8}けん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.8828125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.046875,635)\an8}て
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.26,0:03:22.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.078125,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.37,0:03:44.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9375,635)\an8}ぷん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.37,0:03:44.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.953125,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.37,0:03:44.84,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(720.140625,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.12,0:03:51.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.12,0:03:51.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}こうこうせい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.12,0:03:51.96,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(720.1328125,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.96,0:03:54.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}かんきゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.96,0:03:54.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}めずら
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.96,0:03:54.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}あつ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.96,0:03:54.99,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.6484375,635)\an8}あいだ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:04:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}りょう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:04:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}ちゅうもくど
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:04:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}たか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:04:00.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(802.6796875,635)\an8}なかむらくん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:03.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.53,0:04:03.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.59,0:04:05.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}せつめい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.59,0:04:05.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0703125,635)\an8}ふよう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.52,0:04:06.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}きみ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.52,0:04:06.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.47,0:04:09.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.453125,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.47,0:04:09.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.484375,635)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.61,0:04:11.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}べんきょう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.61,0:04:11.40,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}ゆ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.56,0:04:13.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}しごと
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.93,0:04:17.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(514.38671875,635)\an8}しんにゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.93,0:04:17.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(580.69140625,635)\an8}しゃいん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.93,0:04:17.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.93,0:04:17.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}ちかごろ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.91,0:04:20.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.91,0:04:20.76,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}おうだんまく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.05,0:04:22.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}じょうしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.50,0:04:24.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.96875,635)\an8}かこ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.50,0:04:24.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}ねんかん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.17,0:04:28.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(164.8359375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.17,0:04:28.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(239.875,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.17,0:04:28.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}しゅつじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.17,0:04:28.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0625,635)\an8}のが
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.42,0:04:31.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}おうじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.42,0:04:31.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.42,0:04:31.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.93,0:04:34.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.93,0:04:34.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}れんぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.76,0:04:36.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}さいだい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.62,0:04:39.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.62,0:04:39.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.90625,635)\an8}ふじま
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.62,0:04:39.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}ひき
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.62,0:04:39.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}やぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.62,0:04:39.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}いま
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.359375,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.3828125,635)\an8}れんぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.4296875,635)\an8}まちが
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.6015625,635)\an8}おおかた
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.6484375,635)\an8}よそう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.87,0:04:46.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.87,0:04:46.13,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}ちが
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.56,0:04:48.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}はらん
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.56,0:04:48.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.71,0:04:52.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.71,0:04:52.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.046875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.71,0:04:52.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}やぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.13,0:05:02.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}ちから
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.13,0:05:02.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.46875,635)\an8}わたし
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.13,0:05:02.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}かれ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.13,0:05:02.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}はか
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.81,0:05:04.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}いったい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.81,0:05:04.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}つよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.81,0:05:04.97,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}も
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(266.73828125,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(318.03515625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(519.91015625,635)\an8}ひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.97265625,635)\an8}パーセント
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9453125,635)\an8}かれ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.43,0:05:11.95,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}ひゃく
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}さ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}れんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(194.84375,635)\an8}わず
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}いってん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.79,0:05:34.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(720.1328125,635)\an8}じあい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.25,0:05:37.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}はらん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.85,0:05:39.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}みちすう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.85,0:05:39.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0546875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.24,0:05:41.38,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.05,0:05:43.26,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}よう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.33,0:05:46.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}しゅうかん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.33,0:05:46.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5546875,635)\an8}きしゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.33,0:05:46.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(667.6015625,635)\an8}あいだ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.33,0:05:46.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(727.6328125,635)\an8}やよい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(209.8515625,635)\an8}じつ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}りょうなん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.9609375,635)\an8}ぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}あいだ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}ひこいち
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.63,0:05:51.06,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}あね
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.08,0:05:59.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}きょう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.08,0:05:59.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.08,0:05:59.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.64,0:06:02.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.9140625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.64,0:06:02.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}おどろ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.64,0:06:02.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}しょうじき
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.01,0:06:10.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}あせ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.01,0:06:10.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.06,0:06:24.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.921875,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.06,0:06:24.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}かんとく
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.24,0:06:29.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}あわ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.24,0:06:29.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.24,0:06:29.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}じかん
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.15,0:06:33.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(247.375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.15,0:06:33.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.15,0:06:33.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}どんよく
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.34,0:06:35.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}へん
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.34,0:06:35.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}づら
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.22,0:06:37.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}ちょうじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.22,0:06:37.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.23,0:06:39.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.23,0:06:39.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.78,0:06:41.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}ことし
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.78,0:06:41.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.78,0:06:41.55,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}いちばん
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.82,0:06:45.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.4609375,635)\an8}きょう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.82,0:06:45.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.82,0:06:45.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.21,0:06:47.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.21,0:06:47.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}で
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.21,0:06:47.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.046875,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.98,0:06:49.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.98,0:06:49.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}しら
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.81,0:06:54.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.8828125,635)\an8}けっこう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.81,0:06:54.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9296875,635)\an8}けっこう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.81,0:06:54.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.0390625,635)\an8}いっさい
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.81,0:06:54.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.0859375,635)\an8}ひつよう
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.36,0:06:56.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}じん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}くも
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}うえ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}そんざい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.05,0:07:07.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.0703125,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.52,0:07:11.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}て
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.52,0:07:11.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}の
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.52,0:07:11.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}と
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.52,0:07:11.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.62,0:07:13.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.8984375,635)\an8}とど
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.62,0:07:13.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}そんざい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.62,0:07:13.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.98,0:07:17.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}じっせき
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.98,0:07:17.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.98,0:07:17.82,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}たし
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.61,0:07:20.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}かこ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.61,0:07:20.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}じっせき
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.61,0:07:20.11,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.57,0:07:23.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.57,0:07:23.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.57,0:07:23.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}ち
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.57,0:07:23.00,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}ちが
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.96,0:07:25.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.54,0:07:28.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.54,0:07:28.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}ね
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.54,0:07:28.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.046875,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.85,0:07:30.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}ひ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.85,0:07:30.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}そうぞう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:36.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:36.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}かながわ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:36.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5,635)\an8}おうじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:36.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:36.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.5859375,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}しゅつじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.4765625,635)\an8}たたか
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(637.578125,635)\an8}まいばん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(697.6171875,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:41.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(757.6484375,635)\an8}えが
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.91,0:07:45.83,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}いちねん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.07,0:07:51.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}ぜったい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.07,0:07:51.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.80,0:08:05.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}はるこ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.15,0:08:10.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}さい
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.15,0:08:10.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}ぜんれつ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.15,0:08:10.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}かくほ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.97,0:08:17.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}こんかい
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.97,0:08:17.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.97,0:08:17.33,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.43,0:08:18.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.43,0:08:18.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}しょう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.48,0:08:21.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.48,0:08:21.05,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}ばんちょう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.01,0:08:28.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.01,0:08:28.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}がんば
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.76,0:08:31.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(450.4765625,635)\an8}みうら
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.76,0:08:31.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(486.765625,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.96,0:08:33.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.9140625,635)\an8}かいだん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.96,0:08:33.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}にだん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.96,0:08:33.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}お
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.76,0:08:44.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.64,0:08:51.71,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}ふじま
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.77,0:09:01.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.5234375,635)\an8}ぷん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.77,0:09:01.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.5390625,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.78,0:09:02.92,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}よう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.41,0:09:42.04,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.36,0:09:44.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.11,0:09:45.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.21,0:09:57.56,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.70,0:10:07.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(506.87890625,635)\an8}しじょう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.70,0:10:07.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(573.18359375,635)\an8}さいきょう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.70,0:10:07.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}ことし
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.70,0:10:07.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.88,0:10:09.57,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.00,0:10:16.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}きよた
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.00,0:10:16.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}のぶなが
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.00,0:10:16.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.75,0:10:20.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(277.390625,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.75,0:10:20.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}えら
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.24,0:10:22.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(292.3984375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.24,0:10:22.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.24,0:10:22.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.70,0:10:32.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.70,0:10:32.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.60,0:10:34.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.921875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.60,0:10:34.53,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}えら
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.09,0:10:43.86,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}はや
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.22,0:10:53.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}おのれ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.9765625,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.03125,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.44,0:11:00.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.09375,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.61,0:11:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}ひと
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.61,0:11:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.61,0:11:13.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.6015625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.94,0:11:35.35,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}は
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.67,0:11:39.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}へん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.67,0:11:39.16,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.37,0:11:48.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}るかわ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.01,0:11:50.18,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}るかわ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.92,0:12:22.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.984375,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.07,0:12:25.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9375,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.72,0:12:28.32,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}あき
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.53,0:12:29.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.60,0:12:31.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.60,0:12:31.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(577.5546875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.89,0:12:35.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}ぼうりょく
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.89,0:12:35.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.89,0:12:35.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.89,0:12:35.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.89,0:12:35.69,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}じけん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.91,0:12:38.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9296875,635)\an8}るかわくん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.91,0:12:38.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}だめ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.91,0:12:38.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.0546875,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.15,0:12:40.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(367.4375,635)\an8}おもしれ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.16,0:12:42.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(179.8359375,635)\an8}すけ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.16,0:12:42.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.90625,635)\an8}ひつよう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.16,0:12:42.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.16,0:12:42.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(765.15625,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.43,0:12:50.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.43,0:12:50.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.5546875,635)\an8}い
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.74,0:12:59.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.74,0:12:59.03,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.23,0:13:13.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}は
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.52,0:13:47.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.52,0:13:47.02,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.08,0:13:49.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(585.0625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.12,0:13:52.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}がんば
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.12,0:13:52.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.75,0:13:54.59,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}はな
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.70,0:13:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9296875,635)\an8}いったい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.70,0:13:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.70,0:13:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(465,635)\an8}かんが
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.25,0:14:11.15,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.0234375,635)\an8}るかわ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.47,0:14:14.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.30,0:14:18.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.07,0:15:01.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}こうこうせい
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.07,0:15:01.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(705.125,635)\an8}ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(506.87890625,635)\an8}きょうつう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(558.17578125,635)\an8}てん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.921875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(239.875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}おお
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.08,0:15:07.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.0703125,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.39,0:15:09.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.39,0:15:09.39,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}あかぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.32,0:15:13.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}きょうりょく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.32,0:15:13.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(187.34375,635)\an8}りょう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.32,0:15:13.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.453125,635)\an8}ゆ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.32,0:15:13.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(652.59375,635)\an8}だいこくばしら
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.84,0:15:19.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}ふたり
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.84,0:15:19.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.015625,635)\an8}ある
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.84,0:15:19.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.09375,635)\an8}みち
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.21,0:15:20.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}じつ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.21,0:15:20.66,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}たいしょうてき
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.29,0:15:26.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(239.8671875,635)\an8}ひとり
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.29,0:15:26.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9375,635)\an8}ねん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.29,0:15:26.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(570.0546875,635)\an8}かいぶつ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.29,0:15:26.25,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(675.109375,635)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:28.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.8984375,635)\an8}つね
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:28.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}はし
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:28.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}つづ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.57,0:15:28.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(675.1015625,635)\an8}おとこ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.40,0:15:33.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}ひとり
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.40,0:15:33.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.09375,635)\an8}そしつ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.40,0:15:33.47,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(720.1328125,635)\an8}も
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.77,0:15:36.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.3515625,635)\an8}じつりょくてき
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.77,0:15:36.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4375,635)\an8}けんない
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.77,0:15:36.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.46875,635)\an8}くっし
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.04,0:15:40.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(397.453125,635)\an8}めぐ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.04,0:15:40.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}う
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.04,0:15:40.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}つづ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.04,0:15:40.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(772.65625,635)\an8}おとこ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.62,0:15:44.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5078125,635)\an8}しつれい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.28,0:15:54.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}やろう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.47,0:15:55.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.47,0:15:55.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.58,0:15:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(307.3984375,635)\an8}まった
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.58,0:15:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.4765625,635)\an8}かんが
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.58,0:15:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.58,0:15:59.67,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.5859375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.97,0:16:02.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.75,0:16:06.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.875,635)\an8}きみ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.75,0:16:06.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.24,0:16:12.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.64,0:16:13.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}こうこう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.57,0:16:19.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}くち
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.57,0:16:19.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.57,0:16:19.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}かた
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.57,0:16:19.46,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}ちゅうい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.18,0:16:21.50,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}こうこう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.27,0:16:25.48,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.23,0:16:28.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(472.5,635)\an8}げつ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.23,0:16:28.19,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}た
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.18,0:16:38.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}こうこう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.18,0:16:38.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}さいご
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.18,0:16:38.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}ことし
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.93,0:16:43.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.8984375,635)\an8}あかぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.93,0:16:43.07,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(660.1015625,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.08,0:16:49.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.26,0:16:59.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(645.0859375,635)\an8}え
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.77,0:17:22.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.4140625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.77,0:17:22.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.77,0:17:22.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(757.6640625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.71,0:17:34.51,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:18:04.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.08,0:18:10.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(529.39453125,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.08,0:18:10.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(580.69140625,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.08,0:18:10.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(382.4453125,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.95,0:18:13.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.95,0:18:13.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}きぶん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.13,0:18:16.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}ゆうめいじん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.09,0:18:19.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}めえ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.09,0:18:19.70,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}わ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.50,0:18:37.54,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}ねら
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.02,0:18:43.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(337.421875,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.49,0:18:50.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.48,0:18:52.73,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.30,0:19:00.79,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}じん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.55,0:19:05.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}じん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.77,0:19:08.42,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}のぶなが
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.51,0:19:11.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(487.5,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.51,0:19:11.12,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(562.546875,635)\an8}さる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.30,0:19:12.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}だれ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.30,0:19:12.58,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.60,0:19:13.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}ま
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.60,0:19:13.52,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.64,0:19:15.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(352.4296875,635)\an8}さる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.64,0:19:15.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(563.0390625,635)\an8}あかげ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.64,0:19:15.27,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(599.328125,635)\an8}ざる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.46,0:19:16.28,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.20,0:19:19.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.984375,635)\an8}なに
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.94,0:19:22.81,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}たか
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.06,0:19:25.75,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}さくらぎくん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.77,0:19:28.08,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(412.4609375,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.99,0:19:33.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}ある
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.24,0:19:43.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}も
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.24,0:19:43.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.09375,635)\an8}さんぽ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.24,0:19:43.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(682.6328125,635)\an8}ある
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.52,0:19:46.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.921875,635)\an8}しょほ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.52,0:19:46.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}しょほ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.52,0:19:46.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}しょほ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.59,0:19:50.85,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(592.5625,635)\an8}たす
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.97,0:19:55.64,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.24,0:20:06.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(329.9140625,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.24,0:20:06.93,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(615.078125,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.40,0:20:09.17,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(434.9765625,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.29,0:20:11.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(284.890625,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.29,0:20:11.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.9453125,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.08,0:20:15.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(224.859375,635)\an8}しょうよう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.08,0:20:15.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.8984375,635)\an8}か
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.15,0:20:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}なん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.15,0:20:18.20,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}こ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.84,0:20:19.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(484.125,635)\an8}すう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.84,0:20:19.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(520.90625,635)\an8}びょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.84,0:20:19.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(427.46875,635)\an8}かいし
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.94,0:20:21.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}かんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.94,0:20:21.65,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.0390625,635)\an8}ぬ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.12,0:20:24.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}きあい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.12,0:20:24.89,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.9921875,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.90,0:20:25.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}あ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.90,0:20:25.78,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(510.015625,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.22,0:20:27.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(359.9375,635)\an8}まえ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.22,0:20:27.60,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.17,0:20:31.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}てんさい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.17,0:20:31.90,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(540.03125,635)\an8}ぐもん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.37,0:20:35.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.921875,635)\an8}とうぜん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.37,0:20:35.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(419.96875,635)\an8}きあい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.37,0:20:35.24,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(480.0078125,635)\an8}はい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.61,0:20:41.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.0078125,635)\an8}けっしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.61,0:20:41.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(404.9609375,635)\an8}ちゅうもく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.61,0:20:41.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.078125,635)\an8}だい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.61,0:20:41.29,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(675.109375,635)\an8}せん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.875,635)\an8}しょうほく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(314.9140625,635)\an8}たい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(374.953125,635)\an8}かいなん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.9921875,635)\an8}だいふぞく
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(555.046875,635)\an8}しあい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:45.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(630.0859375,635)\an8}はじ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.16,0:20:48.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(442.484375,635)\an8}りょうこう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.16,0:20:48.80,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}せんしゅ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.91,0:20:51.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(262.3828125,635)\an8}かいし
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.91,0:20:51.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}そうそう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.91,0:20:51.37,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(697.6171875,635)\an8}れんぱつ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.74,0:20:53.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(457.4921875,635)\an8}だいかんしゅう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.74,0:20:53.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}め
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.74,0:20:53.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(607.5703125,635)\an8}うば
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.50,0:20:59.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(254.8828125,635)\an8}はらん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.50,0:20:59.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(344.9296875,635)\an8}まくあ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.50,0:20:59.36,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(449.984375,635)\an8}よ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.51,0:21:01.09,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}き
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.46,0:22:43.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}み
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.46,0:22:43.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(547.5390625,635)\an8}おう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.46,0:22:43.61,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(622.578125,635)\an8}じつりょく
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.72,0:22:44.74,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(517.5234375,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.83,0:22:47.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(202.3515625,635)\an8}さくらぎ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.83,0:22:47.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(682.609375,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.83,0:22:47.49,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(742.640625,635)\an8}し
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.85,0:22:48.88,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}そっこう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.22,0:22:50.43,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(502.515625,635)\an8}しょうぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.76,0:22:55.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(134.8125,635)\an8}まき
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.76,0:22:55.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(299.90625,635)\an8}めえ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.76,0:22:55.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.015625,635)\an8}ぶれいもの
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.76,0:22:55.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(600.0703125,635)\an8}あいて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.76,0:22:55.01,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(765.15625,635)\an8}おも
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.09,0:22:56.31,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(532.53125,635)\an8}のざる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.58,0:22:57.98,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(322.4140625,635)\an8}かながわ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.04,0:22:59.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(464.9921875,635)\an8}おれ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.04,0:22:59.14,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(525.0234375,635)\an8}たお
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.58,0:23:03.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(567.1953125,635)\an8}はなみち
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.58,0:23:03.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(648.015625,635)\an8}ぜっこうちょう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.58,0:23:03.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(450.0078125,635)\an8}けいさん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.58,0:23:03.21,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(495.03125,635)\an8}がい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.38,0:23:04.62,JP-furigana,NTP,0,0,0,,{\pos(389.953125,635)\an8}み