[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 8
Video Position: 2879
Last Style Storage: Default
Video File: [c2club][PokeMon][x264_aac]63.mp4
Audio File: ?video

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,FZShaoEr-M11S,28,&H0FFFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00444444,&H00444444,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,5,5,10,1
Style: other,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00444444,&H00444444,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,5,5,10,1
Style: Default2,FZShaoEr-M11S,28,&H0FFFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00444444,&H00444444,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,5,5,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.80,0:00:05.35,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(100,70)\fad(350,350)\fnTahoma}C2CLUB\N{\fs16}WWW.C2CLUB.NET
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.90,0:01:31.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智一行人继续旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.80,0:01:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又回来常磐市了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.60,0:01:35.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,目的地是常磐道馆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.90,0:01:37.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第八枚徽章就在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.80,0:01:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,常磐市 好久没来了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.70,0:01:46.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 小精灵中心重建了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.70,0:01:47.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.10,0:01:49.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.30,0:01:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是绿色徽章所在的常磐道馆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.84,0:01:59.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\b1\bord0\shad0\fs24\clip(96,167,98,315)\t(0,1590,\clip(96,167,385,315)\c&H062F00&)\pos(98,267)}常磐道馆！最后的徽章！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.71,0:01:59.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\frx180\fs24\1c&H062F00&\bord0\shad0\pos(351,265)}▲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.30,0:02:06.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我终于来到这儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.40,0:02:09.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第八枚徽章·绿色徽章就在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.80,0:02:12.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要得到它
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.80,0:02:16.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好热 今天我燃烧斗志了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.00,0:02:20.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智这家伙真的烧起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.60,0:02:24.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 你们在这里生火干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.20,0:02:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好烫 好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.83,0:02:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你在干嘛 皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.80,0:02:34.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.50,0:02:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你是想要为我的心点燃热火对不对
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.40,0:02:43.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会辜负你热烈的友情的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.40,0:02:51.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好 这就是男人的友情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.00,0:02:53.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全无法理解啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.50,0:02:59.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还是老样子 上演无聊的爆笑剧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.65,0:03:00.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智君
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.10,0:03:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂 小茂真是棒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.50,0:03:05.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂 小茂真是帅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.90,0:03:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小…小茂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.80,0:03:09.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我本来以为你已经放弃成为小精灵大师
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.80,0:03:12.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早滚回真新镇了 结果呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.50,0:03:14.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你能够来到这里 算是值得嘉奖了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.70,0:03:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.00,0:03:17.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要太激动 小智
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.90,0:03:19.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是照你这个情况嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.40,0:03:22.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你还没有搜集到八枚徽章对不对
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.30,0:03:24.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂 你有资格说我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.10,0:03:27.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.10,0:03:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我得到的徽章已经有十枚了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.90,0:03:36.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小精灵联盟的出场权早就拿到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.70,0:03:40.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我今天是回去真新镇刚好顺路
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.90,0:03:44.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来跟这里的馆主切磋一下功夫的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.30,0:03:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是真新镇的小茂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.30,0:03:51.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来跟馆主正式挑战了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.70,0:03:57.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.20,0:03:59.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也进去吧 皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.40,0:04:05.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,按规定 小精灵决斗 一次只能一个人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.70,0:04:06.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.20,0:04:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是规定
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.00,0:04:13.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,照这样下去的话 我一定会被小茂超前的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.20,0:04:17.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是你本来就一直被小茂超前啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.00,0:04:22.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你讲话太毒了吧 小霞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.70,0:04:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是实话实说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.90,0:04:27.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我确实说不定是倒数第一名
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.50,0:04:31.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我已经尽我的力量努力加油了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.40,0:04:34.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.40,0:04:38.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在能够了解我心情的就只有你了 皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.60,0:04:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.30,0:04:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么对我的波克比做这种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.80,0:05:00.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我是因为小霞…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.40,0:05:02.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 是一时惊吓
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.61,0:05:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.90,0:05:04.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.80,0:05:11.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些小鬼头跑哪里去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.90,0:05:14.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们再不快点抓到那只皮卡丘的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.70,0:05:17.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们可能会被火箭队给开除的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.00,0:05:22.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.65,0:05:24.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么喵喵
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.42,0:05:27.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喵喵我什么事也没有做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.80,0:05:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骗人 你刚才明明踢我的屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.80,0:05:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 我才没有兴趣踢你的屁股呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.40,0:05:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.40,0:05:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们的好运气到了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.40,0:05:43.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把这只波克比拿去送给老大的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.70,0:05:45.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.40,0:05:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们过去的负债一笔勾销了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.70,0:05:53.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 也许会变成这样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.20,0:05:56.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过来过来…可爱的波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.30,0:06:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等一下 波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.00,0:06:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比 不能过去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.50,0:06:04.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.80,0:06:06.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那边危险啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.20,0:06:07.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,掉下去就糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.40,0:06:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小波克比 过来这边嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.70,0:06:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了还债 我只好追过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.50,0:06:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 加油 武藏…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.00,0:06:21.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 加油 武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.10,0:06:21.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Fight
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.73,0:06:22.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.80,0:06:24.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把我当成杂耍的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.40,0:06:27.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底以为我是为了什么这么拼命的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.30,0:06:37.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.00,0:06:46.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.30,0:06:48.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得到波克比了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.90,0:06:55.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂 小茂真是棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.50,0:06:57.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂 小茂真是帅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.80,0:07:01.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是常磐道馆的训练家 坂木
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.90,0:07:04.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是真新镇第一的小茂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.50,0:07:06.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挺精神的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.20,0:07:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我就接受你的挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.20,0:07:12.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用的小精灵限定三只
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.00,0:07:13.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,时间没有限制
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.10,0:07:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正式比赛开始
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.90,0:07:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看你的 尼多王
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.80,0:07:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 隆隆岩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.90,0:07:27.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隆隆岩 使出撞击
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.70,0:07:33.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼多王 以撞击对抗撞击吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.30,0:07:43.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隆隆岩无法战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.40,0:07:48.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赢了赢了 小茂赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.00,0:07:52.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挺有一套的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.50,0:07:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么接着用它吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.70,0:07:59.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 这是你的打算
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.30,0:08:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨钳蟹 铗子小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.60,0:08:04.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,强力的钳拥有一万马力的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.90,0:08:06.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨钳蟹 使用大钳槌
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.10,0:08:15.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回来吧 尼多王
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.70,0:08:18.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的小精灵培育得不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.50,0:08:22.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我的甜心不会输给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.50,0:08:24.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看你的 风速狗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.90,0:08:28.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,风速狗 用猛撞攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.00,0:08:33.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来用火焰漩涡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.20,0:08:40.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂 好棒 小茂 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.70,0:08:43.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的小茂最厉害了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.90,0:08:46.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们 各位美丽的女朋友们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.30,0:08:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我不能再让女孩子等太久了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.40,0:08:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给它最后的一招 大字爆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.30,0:09:06.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨钳蟹无法战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.00,0:09:10.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赢了赢了 打赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.50,0:09:13.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂小茂好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.10,0:09:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再打下去你是白费力气的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.40,0:09:17.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.20,0:09:19.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那可不一定
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.80,0:09:20.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.00,0:09:23.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有绝对厉害的力量呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.90,0:09:26.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在就让你见识一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.30,0:09:43.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,风速狗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.50,0:09:45.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这…这家伙到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.60,0:09:48.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有资料 是神秘的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.40,0:09:50.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有资料
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.70,0:09:52.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,儿戏的道馆比赛到此结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.00,0:09:55.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小弟弟 就算你拥有的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.90,0:09:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起对付它 也赢不了它的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.40,0:10:02.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才没有那种事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.60,0:10:04.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然你要试试看吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.80,0:10:07.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 上吧 尼多王
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.50,0:10:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,风速狗 又要拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.80,0:10:11.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让那个小弟弟尝一尝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.80,0:10:14.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么叫做真正的恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.60,0:10:19.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尼多王 风速狗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.80,0:10:20.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吧 小弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.40,0:10:23.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这才是真正的恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.10,0:10:26.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是绝对无敌的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.61,0:10:34.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\bord2\shad0\fs35\3c&H000000&\be10\c&H91EBE5&\pos(443,168)}我是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.07,0:10:40.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\bord2\shad0\fs35\3c&H000000&\c&H91EBE5&\be10\pos(454,158)}风速狗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.07,0:10:40.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\pos(6,299)}{\pos(25,316)}{\fs22}№ 059  风速狗\N身高：1.9m\N体重：155kg\N属性：火\N特性：威吓·延烧\N分类：传说小精灵\N在中国的传说中登场的\N小精灵。跑动的速度十分惊人。
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.90,0:10:45.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老大 今天我们得到了非常棒的小精灵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.50,0:10:49.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比那只皮卡丘还要少见的小精灵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.50,0:10:51.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们终于抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.90,0:10:53.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.10,0:10:57.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们找到很少见的小精灵了 您看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.20,0:11:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那东西有什么能力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.50,0:11:06.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它有什么能力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.50,0:11:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.40,0:11:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.70,0:11:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它有缓和现场气氛的强力绝招
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.00,0:11:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.50,0:11:19.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们一直以来都在干些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.60,0:11:21.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丢脸的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.90,0:11:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原谅啊 老大
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.60,0:11:27.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.90,0:11:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.80,0:11:31.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.40,0:11:34.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,临时有急事了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.00,0:11:36.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这间道馆暂时交给你们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.30,0:11:38.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,交给我们是指…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.30,0:11:43.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我回来以前 你们就用这些保护道馆
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.80,0:11:51.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说来…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.20,0:11:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这间道馆的馆主
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.90,0:11:55.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是我们呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.70,0:11:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.10,0:12:07.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在要借用你的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.40,0:12:09.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.40,0:12:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比 你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.50,0:12:27.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快出来啊 波克比 你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.80,0:12:29.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.20,0:12:30.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比 快点回答
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.50,0:12:34.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.00,0:12:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到处都没有 不知道到哪儿去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.80,0:12:41.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比现在一定孤零零的 不知道在哪里哭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.79,0:12:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 波克比要是有个三长两短
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.10,0:12:46.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会原谅你的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.30,0:12:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小霞 不要那么冲动嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小刚 你闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.20,0:12:50.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.60,0:12:55.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.90,0:13:00.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.60,0:13:02.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一 二
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.80,0:13:07.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,波克比
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.60,0:13:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 你害我担心死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.60,0:13:15.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是它为什么会在这个地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.70,0:13:17.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 你看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.30,0:13:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.20,0:13:23.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位漂亮姐姐们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.10,0:13:26.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,振作一点 小茂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.10,0:13:29.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂 到底发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.00,0:13:34.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我被从没有见过的小精灵给打败了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.60,0:13:37.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是力量超级强的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.60,0:13:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的小精灵们完全没有办法对抗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.10,0:13:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然有强到让小茂没有办法对抗的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.30,0:13:48.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂少爷输了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.40,0:13:55.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过输了一场而已 有什么好哭的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.70,0:14:00.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,每输一场就哭一次的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.50,0:14:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智早就哭成人干了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.30,0:14:06.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪有这么说的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.40,0:14:11.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,任何人都不可能赢过它的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.70,0:14:12.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小茂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.70,0:14:16.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.80,0:14:18.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你诚心诚意地发问了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.20,0:14:20.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们就大发慈悲地告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.50,0:14:23.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了防止世界被破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.80,0:14:25.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护世界的和平
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.30,0:14:28.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贯彻爱与真实的邪恶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.80,0:14:30.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可爱又迷人的反派角色
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.30,0:14:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.30,0:14:32.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.50,0:14:35.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 搞什么鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.60,0:14:37.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别在最高潮的一刻抢我们的台词
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.00,0:14:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁叫你们老是用同一套台词啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.90,0:14:42.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天我们旧瓶换新酒了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.20,0:14:45.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天我们跟平时可是大不相同哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.50,0:14:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.50,0:14:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们大海浪加小海浪什么大浪都历经过来 终于有今天了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.10,0:14:54.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听了可不要吓到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.70,0:14:56.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这间道馆的馆主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.30,0:14:58.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我们哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.30,0:14:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.40,0:15:01.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们就是馆主
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.10,0:15:04.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对 就在今天
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.10,0:15:07.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚我们两个人奉命被派来接管这个道馆了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.10,0:15:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.00,0:15:10.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绿色徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.10,0:15:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说 这间道馆是火箭队的咯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.20,0:15:15.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么火箭队会…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.10,0:15:17.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们这些小鬼头是不会了解的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.10,0:15:20.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们火箭队有个崇高远大的目标
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.20,0:15:22.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:24.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你问我到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.50,0:15:26.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.60,0:15:29.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之就是很远大的目标
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.20,0:15:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实他们自己也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.10,0:15:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 想要绿色徽章的话 就打倒我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.40,0:15:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求之不得
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.60,0:15:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次为了你们特别设了很不一样的擂台
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.70,0:15:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快点进来训练家的战斗位置吧 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.00,0:15:53.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 这个是陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.80,0:15:55.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们一定是事先设下了什么机关
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.20,0:15:59.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,逃避的话 就算是放弃比赛 判你输哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.10,0:16:02.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会逃避放弃的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.30,0:16:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,时间没有限制
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.80,0:16:09.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用的小精灵以三只为限 怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.58,0:16:11.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.70,0:16:13.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧 我的仆人们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.80,0:16:26.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很不错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.80,0:16:27.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太厉害了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.34,0:16:30.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被吓到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.90,0:16:33.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 小心点 这次跟平常不一样哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.90,0:16:36.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 杰尼龟 决定是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.00,0:16:42.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,杰尼龟根本就不是它们的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.60,0:16:44.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪力 使用手刀攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.50,0:16:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.30,0:16:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个擂台 设了小精灵受到伤害
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.30,0:16:59.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,训练家也会跟着一起受到伤害的机关哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.80,0:17:02.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小精灵的痛苦你也尝尝看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.00,0:17:05.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 实力差异太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.40,0:17:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妙蛙种子 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.50,0:17:12.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来换巨钳蟹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.30,0:17:13.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攻上去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.40,0:17:17.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妙蛙种子 使用藤鞭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.70,0:17:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨钳蟹 硬邦邦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.20,0:17:28.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有用的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.50,0:17:30.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来一点效果都没有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.10,0:17:32.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巨钳蟹 用泡泡攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.98,0:17:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快住手 小智 实力相差太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.70,0:17:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会放弃的 我相信它们的实力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.48,0:17:48.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.60,0:17:50.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不会输的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.10,0:17:52.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小…小智
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.90,0:17:56.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上吧 比比鸟 使用电光一闪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.80,0:18:02.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁现在快点进攻啊 小智
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.90,0:18:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比比鸟 用舍身攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.40,0:18:16.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小次郎 为什么我们这边也会受到攻击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.20,0:18:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.50,0:18:19.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小次郎啊 小次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.60,0:18:22.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有想到我们也会输嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.00,0:18:26.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我早料到会这样 也设下了反败为胜的机关哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.10,0:18:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就用这个 把它们一次炸得远远的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.70,0:18:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不准你们做出卑鄙的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.60,0:18:37.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管那么多了 发动总攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.70,0:18:39.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿柏怪 双弹瓦斯 上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.00,0:18:45.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,使用新的小精灵 犯规了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.90,0:18:48.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这间道馆里我就代表规则
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.00,0:18:50.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 哪有这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.80,0:18:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皮卡丘 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.70,0:19:17.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打赢了 我们竟然打赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.00,0:19:22.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位 谢谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.40,0:19:23.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这都是你们的功劳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.20,0:19:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智小智好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.90,0:19:29.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智小智好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.60,0:19:32.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智小智好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.20,0:19:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第四名的你 有这种成绩是不错了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.10,0:19:38.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.30,0:19:40.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要对付那只神秘的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.30,0:19:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像现在这样是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.40,0:19:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,武藏 振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.00,0:19:45.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.60,0:19:50.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么只有我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.40,0:19:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎 武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.90,0:19:53.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这场比赛是我赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.80,0:19:55.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,按照我们的约定 绿色徽章给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.40,0:19:58.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.90,0:20:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你这样太狡猾了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.80,0:20:03.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我本来就很狡猾啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.50,0:20:09.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喵 不可以按下那个钮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.90,0:20:17.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们这边也顺便设了机关
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.60,0:20:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.40,0:20:25.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好讨厌的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.70,0:20:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 我得到绿色徽章了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.70,0:20:39.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这间道馆要垮了 大家快点逃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.20,0:21:04.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是小茂所说的神秘的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.90,0:21:06.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么家伙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.60,0:21:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比起那个
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.00,0:21:10.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我终于集齐八枚徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.60,0:21:12.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,具有小精灵联盟的出场资格了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.20,0:21:15.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们快点去参加联盟大会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.70,0:21:18.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 我们大家一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.50,0:21:20.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大会在什么地方举行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.50,0:21:21.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道耶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.20,0:21:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个人就是太迷糊了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.30,0:21:26.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们去问问大木博士怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.20,0:21:28.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好主意耶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.50,0:21:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们现在就回真新镇去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.50,0:21:31.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.60,0:21:35.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于得到期待已久的八枚徽章的小智等人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.40,0:21:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,向家乡真新镇的方向
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.90,0:21:41.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神采飞扬地跨步开走了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.09,0:23:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这次的小精灵是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.17,0:23:14.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皮…皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.56,0:23:20.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说到004号 就是小火龙
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.43,0:23:24.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然每个个体之间可能会有差异
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.51,0:23:28.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过小火龙的喷射火焰拥有能烧断厚实铁板的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.22,0:23:33.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根据记录 真的会超过1500度 实在令人惊讶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.02,0:23:39.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并且这火焰也可以进行温度调节 走夜路时也很方便
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.20,0:23:42.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还可以像这样用来烧开水
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.38,0:23:46.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以说是很方便的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.23,0:23:52.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么这里来一句
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.16,0:23:57.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,浮现在 小火龙的火焰中 的人影
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.71,0:24:00.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像不是特别明白
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.31,0:24:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家也要收服宠物小精灵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.10,0:24:10.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真新镇 我的家乡 我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.00,0:24:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小精灵马戏团来了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.00,0:24:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我当然要去看了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.40,0:24:17.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个时候火箭队出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.50,0:24:20.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们的目标当然是马戏团的小精灵了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.10,0:24:21.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不会让你们得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.50,0:24:24.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要保护这些小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.20,0:24:26.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一集 宠物小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.40,0:24:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小精灵马戏团的吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.10,0:24:32.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家也来收服宠物小精灵吧




Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.00,0:02:05.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,此片送给所有喜欢宠物小精灵的朋友们！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.00,0:02:10.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,本字幕仅限试看之用 禁止用于商业行为及未经许可修改任何内容
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.00,0:02:15.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你喜欢本作品 请支持购买正版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.00,0:02:20.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,若因私自散布造成法律问题 C2星之海洋字幕组恕不负责
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.00,0:02:25.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,同时我们严厉谴责一切盗版行为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.00,0:02:30.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,C2小精灵工作组正招募翻译校译人员
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.00,0:02:35.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,有日语翻译能力的朋友如有意加入我们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.00,0:02:40.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,请登录论坛后给 {\fnTahoma}smnliu{\r} 发送悄悄话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.00,0:02:47.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,本集宠物小精灵的制作人员是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.00,0:02:50.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,片源 06_taro     原稿 蓝蓝圆企鹅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.00,0:02:53.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,校译 哀小哀 so-nansu     校对 superbabyXP
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.00,0:02:56.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,时间 キンヤ     特效 meimei
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.00,0:02:59.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,资料 PPK      监督 smnliu & SAP
