[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 8
Video Position: 23564
Last Style Storage: Default
Video File: [c2club][PokeMon][x264_aac]64.mp4
Audio File: ?video

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,FZShaoEr-M11S,28,&H0FFFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00444444,&H00444444,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,5,5,10,1
Style: other,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00444444,&H00444444,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,5,5,10,1
Style: Default2,FZShaoEr-M11S,28,&H0FFFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00444444,&H00444444,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,5,5,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.80,0:00:05.35,Default2,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(100,70)\fad(350,350)\fnTahoma}C2CLUB\N{\fs16}WWW.C2CLUB.NET
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.85,0:01:35.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呼叫中 呼叫中 呼叫中…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.35,0:01:37.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.34,0:01:40.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你打电话过来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.66,0:01:42.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.82,0:01:44.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 原来是留言电话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.25,0:01:46.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有事的人请在哔声响起以后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.38,0:01:48.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进行留言 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.11,0:01:53.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 我很快就会回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.61,0:01:55.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你做好大餐等我回去吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.76,0:02:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\b1\bord0\shad0\fs24\clip(92,167,94,315)\t(0,1630,\clip(92,167,385,315)\c&H062F00&)\pos(94,267)}小精灵马戏团的吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.72,0:02:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\frx180\fs24\1c&H062F00&\bord0\shad0\pos(351,266)}▲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.35,0:02:04.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智得到第八枚徽章
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.07,0:02:08.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于获得了参加小精灵联盟的资格
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.71,0:02:11.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 他的家乡真新镇很快就到了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.34,0:02:14.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小智
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.39,0:02:16.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不用赶那么快吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.16,0:02:17.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.70,0:02:20.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说什么你知道 你都用跑的了 喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.09,0:02:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很快就可以看到真新镇了 皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.12,0:02:28.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.86,0:02:29.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.77,0:02:31.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.57,0:02:33.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这地方有个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.22,0:02:35.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.16,0:02:38.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.05,0:02:39.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.78,0:02:41.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.07,0:02:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是看不见的墙壁吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.19,0:02:45.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…那什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.53,0:02:53.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个家伙是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.60,0:02:56.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶 障碍小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.12,0:02:58.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它用最擅长的哑剧制造出来的墙壁
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.12,0:03:00.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会形成真的墙壁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.70,0:03:02.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,由于发现的案例不多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.60,0:03:04.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多的不明点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.54,0:03:05.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吸盘魔偶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.94,0:03:08.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能够遇到这么少见的小精灵 太幸运了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.12,0:03:12.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 马上把它收服
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.72,0:03:12.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.50,0:03:19.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请让我来收服那只吸盘魔偶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.30,0:03:21.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那怎么可以 这是我先找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.13,0:03:23.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要那么冲动嘛 小智
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.03,0:03:26.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好 第一次见面 在下叫做小刚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.19,0:03:29.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐 那就请你快点收服那只吸盘魔偶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.97,0:03:30.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.79,0:03:32.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点 小姐 快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.74,0:03:35.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要逃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.16,0:03:38.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶 我需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.04,0:03:44.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.04,0:03:48.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小姐 你是不是有什么苦衷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.69,0:03:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.34,0:03:52.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要是我帮得上忙 尽管开口说吧 没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.55,0:03:58.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小精灵马戏团
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.73,0:04:00.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好玩的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.41,0:04:03.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是这个小精灵马戏团的团长 亚津子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.77,0:04:07.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚津子 你好厉害哦 这么年轻就当了团长
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.81,0:04:08.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,团长
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.66,0:04:10.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.66,0:04:12.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新的吸盘魔偶找到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.38,0:04:14.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.62,0:04:18.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 公演已经快到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.12,0:04:23.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们请看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.80,0:04:27.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.15,0:04:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是样子不太对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.91,0:04:30.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,懒成那副德行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.94,0:04:33.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是我不对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.29,0:04:37.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我太溺爱它了 使它变得太过任性
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.72,0:04:39.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连马戏团的练习它都不参加
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.38,0:04:41.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后变成了那副德行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.51,0:04:44.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是你培育的方式不对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.99,0:04:48.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我无论如何也想要让它重新振作起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.15,0:04:51.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才需要竞争对手来刺激它
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.35,0:04:52.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.58,0:04:55.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才想要另外抓一只吸盘魔偶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.99,0:04:56.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.90,0:05:00.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,确实 小智对小茂就异常热衷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.81,0:05:02.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说小茂怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.49,0:05:04.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙哪算是我的劲敌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.39,0:05:05.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.58,0:05:09.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 这个就包在我身上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.41,0:05:10.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗 小刚先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.23,0:05:12.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.42,0:05:13.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.87,0:05:15.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就完全放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.10,0:05:20.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又来了 小刚这个人没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.82,0:05:23.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你打算怎么抓住那只吸盘魔偶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.89,0:05:28.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本不需要抓 只要制作就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.15,0:05:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,制作…你是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.25,0:05:34.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 你不要担心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.40,0:05:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把你的身体交给我小刚大人来处理吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.61,0:05:40.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把身体交给你…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.49,0:05:58.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坂木老大
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.46,0:06:02.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,武藏 小次郎还有喵喵来找您了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.16,0:06:04.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.30,0:06:07.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,常磐道馆的事情请原谅我们 坂木老大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.42,0:06:08.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次我们一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.61,0:06:10.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会抓来很厉害的小精灵的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.34,0:06:12.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我忙得很
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.94,0:06:15.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要为了这种无聊的小事情来找我罗嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.45,0:06:20.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是是…非常对不起 坂木老大 我们失陪了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.32,0:06:25.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你才是终极的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.53,0:06:27.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要有你在的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.26,0:06:36.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然没责怪我们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.66,0:06:38.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一次算我们走运
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.54,0:06:40.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了心地宽厚的老大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.96,0:06:43.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定要抓到厉害的小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.23,0:06:44.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.29,0:06:47.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小精灵马戏团
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.19,0:07:02.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许会成功哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.54,0:07:03.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太像了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.91,0:07:07.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好这是我培育的小精灵中最棒的一只
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.07,0:07:10.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不记得你有培育我什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.04,0:07:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然勉强我来扮演
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.10,0:07:16.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干脆小刚你自己来扮演不就行了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.49,0:07:19.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 我的身高太高了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.51,0:07:21.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且我长得太可爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.59,0:07:24.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 这些人真是有够厚脸皮
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.11,0:07:28.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 小智 请你帮个忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.63,0:07:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.48,0:07:30.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.97,0:07:32.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智 你就帮个忙嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.99,0:07:36.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,问题是我根本就不会什么杂耍嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.72,0:07:38.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一点你不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.53,0:07:41.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚津子小姐会温柔又亲切又细心地呵护你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.40,0:07:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手把手地慢慢教你的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.66,0:07:44.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧 亚津子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.73,0:07:46.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.32,0:07:49.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智的话一定很快就学会了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.95,0:07:50.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.27,0:07:52.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了 小智先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.20,0:07:54.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心 我们也会帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.83,0:07:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你们都这么说了 我就做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.79,0:08:01.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么现在就要开始训练了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.55,0:08:04.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.90,0:08:06.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是爱的鞭子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.25,0:08:09.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚津子好像变成另外一个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.87,0:08:12.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 首先是演哑剧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.79,0:08:14.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哑剧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.36,0:08:17.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用再罗嗦了 还不快开始 快点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.02,0:08:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这跟原先讲的不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.82,0:08:23.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么温柔细心地呵护我教导我嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.06,0:08:26.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对 一点也不像
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.08,0:08:29.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得吸盘魔偶会逃避训练
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.19,0:08:31.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她这样太凶了 怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.31,0:08:35.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行 再重新来一次
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.63,0:08:38.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.64,0:08:40.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.47,0:08:46.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,它还是老样子懒在那里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.19,0:08:49.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智的努力对这家伙会有用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.27,0:08:51.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.68,0:09:03.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎各位观众来看小精灵马戏团
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.18,0:09:07.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在呢 小精灵马戏团开幕了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.65,0:09:28.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来了来了 终于等到了耶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.16,0:09:30.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油哦 小智
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.61,0:09:33.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油 小智
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.42,0:09:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.42,0:09:42.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以说话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.51,0:09:47.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.03,0:09:49.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,情况不太对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.77,0:09:51.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这个样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.55,0:09:55.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你诚心诚意地发问了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.17,0:09:58.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们就大发慈悲地告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.62,0:10:00.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了防止世界被破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.74,0:10:02.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护世界的和平
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.78,0:10:05.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贯彻爱与真实的邪恶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.17,0:10:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可爱又迷人的反派角色
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.21,0:10:07.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.06,0:10:09.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.21,0:10:14.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是穿梭在银河的火箭队
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.74,0:10:17.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,白洞 白色的明天在等着我们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.77,0:10:22.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.13,0:10:25.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家鼓掌啊 快鼓掌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.73,0:10:26.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火箭队
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.83,0:10:28.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们到底想要干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.49,0:10:30.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正精彩的现在才要开始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.09,0:10:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那只吸盘魔偶 我要接收
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.14,0:10:35.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么 我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.81,0:10:36.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.88,0:10:38.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁管你行不行
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.20,0:10:40.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不择手段弄到手是我们火箭队的作风
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.07,0:10:41.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看招
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.06,0:10:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚津子 危险
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.76,0:10:50.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火箭队的马戏表演精彩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.85,0:10:53.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.22,0:10:55.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.76,0:10:57.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.12,0:11:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事情怎么会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.50,0:11:02.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小霞 小刚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.19,0:11:04.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是小智的妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.31,0:11:07.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那只吸盘魔偶是小智吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.27,0:11:10.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.65,0:11:12.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.57,0:11:18.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\bord2\shad0\fs35\3c&H000000&\be10\c&H91EBE5&\pos(443,168)}我是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.95,0:11:24.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,0)\bord2\shad0\fs35\3c&H000000&\c&H91EBE5&\be10\pos(469,165)}吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.95,0:11:24.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\pos(32,302)}{\pos(25,316)}{\fs22}№ 122  吸盘魔偶\N身高：1.3m\N体重：54.5kg\N属性：超能力\N特性：隔音·过滤\N分类：障碍小精灵\N善于欺骗人类。演哑剧\N做出的墙会变成真正的墙。
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.84,0:11:29.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智他看起来很不错的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.60,0:11:32.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是小智被火箭队的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.84,0:11:34.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的 小霞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.63,0:11:36.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们的目标是要得到吸盘魔偶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.26,0:11:40.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道其实是小智扮的 很快就会放了他的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.29,0:11:41.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.32,0:11:45.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,火箭队的人不会想得到他们的天敌小智的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.81,0:11:46.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.78,0:11:47.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难得大家碰在一块
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.11,0:11:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到我们家来吧 我请你们吃大餐哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.35,0:11:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.93,0:12:02.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喵哈哈 这次的工作太简单了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.84,0:12:06.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 平时妨碍我们的小鬼头没有出现 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.13,0:12:11.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说 这才是我们火箭队的实力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.07,0:12:14.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老大一定会对我们另眼相看的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.14,0:12:20.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你们早一点发现到好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.38,0:12:23.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.51,0:12:25.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然你诚心诚意地发问了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.48,0:12:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就大发慈悲地告诉你们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.09,0:12:30.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不对…现在不是学你们的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.87,0:12:32.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是你这个小鬼头
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.99,0:12:33.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.57,0:12:36.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你是吸盘魔偶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.69,0:12:37.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道你不想当人了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.14,0:12:39.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在胡说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.81,0:12:41.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我还有很多事情要做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.06,0:12:42.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.49,0:12:46.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 太荒唐了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.28,0:12:49.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么每次都被这个小鬼头打扰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.20,0:12:53.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之收服吸盘魔偶的作战要重新设计了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.81,0:12:57.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别跑 小偷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.99,0:12:59.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们才是小偷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.23,0:13:04.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是小偷 是火箭队
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.69,0:13:07.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你的招待
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.98,0:13:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 别客气
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.52,0:13:11.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们是小智的朋友嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.48,0:13:13.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随时欢迎你们过来玩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.38,0:13:16.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智真幸福 有这么好的妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.24,0:13:16.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.06,0:13:21.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.38,0:13:22.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,保重
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.98,0:13:26.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心一点 以后欢迎随时过来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.51,0:13:35.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说归说 小智那个孩子没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.07,0:13:40.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.27,0:13:44.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你平安无事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.47,0:13:46.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 进来进来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.19,0:13:48.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我从小刚跟小霞他们那里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.65,0:13:50.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道你扮成这个模样的原因了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.20,0:13:55.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的完全进入扮演吸盘魔偶的状态了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.75,0:13:57.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我马上做饭给你吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.82,0:14:03.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 尽量吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.93,0:14:05.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不够的话我会再做的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.26,0:14:22.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈大概很担心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.42,0:14:28.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.99,0:14:30.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都回来了 还在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.29,0:14:36.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智变成两个了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.30,0:14:39.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你在我家做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.56,0:14:43.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.03,0:14:46.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 那是真正的吸盘魔偶啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.14,0:14:48.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的话你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.06,0:14:51.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.79,0:14:55.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就说嘛 怪不得这孩子这么有礼貌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.11,0:14:59.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶 如果有你在的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.31,0:15:01.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就不用假扮成这个样子了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.58,0:15:03.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶 拜托你 跟我一块走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.85,0:15:07.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶 拜托你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.69,0:15:09.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就听小智的话好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.02,0:15:11.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乖孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.54,0:15:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙脸皮有够厚的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.50,0:15:25.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本周不可阻挡的厉害的战斗武器 火箭战车登场咯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.04,0:15:28.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一次我一定要跟他彻彻底底做个了结才行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.78,0:15:31.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马戏团的小精灵全部我们都要收服
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.49,0:15:32.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.94,0:15:35.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,捕获飞弹 预备
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.82,0:15:37.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发射准备 OK
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.08,0:15:38.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发射
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.60,0:15:47.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽量抓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.33,0:15:48.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.46,0:15:56.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.31,0:15:57.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是火箭队
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.95,0:15:59.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那些家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.34,0:16:02.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点带着小精灵逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.59,0:16:03.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.61,0:16:11.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们是逃不掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.32,0:16:18.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.75,0:16:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的吸盘魔偶一定在这里 小次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.36,0:16:26.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.23,0:16:34.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.59,0:16:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别跑 别跑…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.61,0:16:41.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.21,0:16:43.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,振作起来啊 吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.73,0:16:46.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起逃走吧 快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.42,0:17:00.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.32,0:17:01.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要收服你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.88,0:17:03.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,飞弹锁定
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.01,0:17:06.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,捕获飞弹 发…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.69,0:17:07.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.56,0:17:09.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是那个小鬼头
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.70,0:17:11.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.71,0:17:12.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.59,0:17:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来你没事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.19,0:17:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.25,0:17:19.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个太碍事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.29,0:17:20.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,闪开 闪开
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.36,0:17:22.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心我的战车把你们压成肉酱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.46,0:17:23.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想得美
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.17,0:17:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皮卡丘 用十万伏特
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.59,0:17:33.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.74,0:17:39.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这战车是橡胶做的 你的电击是没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.18,0:17:42.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,橡胶是不导电的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.77,0:17:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.02,0:17:46.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样只好赌赌看了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.50,0:17:48.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喷火龙 决定是你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.14,0:17:54.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喷火龙 用喷射火焰
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.44,0:18:00.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.13,0:18:02.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回来吧 喷火龙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.01,0:18:10.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正你的小精灵也只有这种程度而已嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.24,0:18:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不成熟的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.41,0:18:13.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你见识见识我们的实力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.06,0:18:18.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶 你去帮助小智他们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.38,0:18:23.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.65,0:18:26.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发现吸盘魔偶了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.96,0:18:28.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,捕获飞弹 发射
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.72,0:18:29.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我按
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.24,0:18:34.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.65,0:18:35.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.92,0:18:39.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做得好 吸盘魔魔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.78,0:18:45.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 这种墙壁我要撞破它
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.01,0:18:46.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,向前冲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.65,0:18:53.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.03,0:18:58.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有动摇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.30,0:18:59.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,厉害哦 吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.95,0:19:01.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是吸盘魔偶的力量了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.51,0:19:08.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 不能破坏的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.24,0:19:09.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就避开吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.68,0:19:11.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,向右边绕行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.44,0:19:15.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.33,0:19:16.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,向这边来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.29,0:19:17.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.33,0:19:26.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.21,0:19:28.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.53,0:19:32.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要撞破你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.76,0:19:55.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.65,0:19:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.99,0:19:59.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.90,0:20:02.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 吸盘魔魔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.77,0:20:04.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔魔…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.00,0:20:07.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个孩子的名字 很可爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.76,0:20:12.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吸盘魔偶 我就知道你果然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.04,0:20:17.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来是练习的时候我对你太严格了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.90,0:20:18.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.57,0:20:21.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后你愿意继续在马戏团里表演吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.12,0:20:24.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.54,0:20:37.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种烂墙壁 撞破它
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.36,0:20:39.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有飞弹 通通发射
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.68,0:20:40.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.30,0:20:55.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好讨厌的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.47,0:21:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有吸盘魔魔在 我就轻松多了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.80,0:21:12.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来吸盘魔偶这个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.22,0:21:15.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全适应这个家了耶
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.77,0:21:19.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看样子吸盘魔偶比小智还要有用呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.96,0:21:21.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才没那种事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.31,0:21:31.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小智回到好久没踏入的家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.63,0:21:36.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来吸盘魔偶也成了小智的家人了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.47,0:23:11.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 这次的小精灵是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.04,0:23:13.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,皮…皮卡丘
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.81,0:23:20.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说到089号 就是臭臭泥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.01,0:23:26.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臭臭泥拥有在淤泥中也能够存活下去的强韧生命力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.00,0:23:29.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因此在学术界也受到很大关注…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.95,0:23:31.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 快住手 臭臭泥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.33,0:23:35.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我现在还在进行重要的讲解呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.40,0:23:40.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有种说法称 它吸收海中和地底下的有害物质
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.70,0:23:44.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为自然的净化出着一份力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.95,0:23:46.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然味道不怎么好闻
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.68,0:23:49.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过可能就是因为这特殊能力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.84,0:23:52.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么这里来一句
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.72,0:23:56.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臭臭泥 要是和它搞好关系 就不臭了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.13,0:24:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和小精灵搞好关系是好事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.28,0:24:03.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家也要收服宠物小精灵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.85,0:24:07.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于到了圣诞节
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.10,0:24:12.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全世界的孩子都在满心期待着圣诞老人的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.05,0:24:14.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这时却发生了大事件
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.22,0:24:18.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞老人的礼物被火箭队抢走了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.01,0:24:20.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能原谅他们
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.55,0:24:23.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对会夺回礼物的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.93,0:24:26.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一集 宠物小精灵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.03,0:24:28.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迷唇姐的圣诞节
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.35,0:24:31.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都去获取礼物吧



Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.00,0:02:05.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,此片送给所有喜欢宠物小精灵的朋友们！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.00,0:02:10.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,本字幕仅限试看之用 禁止用于商业行为及未经许可修改任何内容
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.00,0:02:15.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你喜欢本作品 请支持购买正版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.00,0:02:20.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,若因私自散布造成法律问题 C2星之海洋字幕组恕不负责
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.00,0:02:25.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,同时我们严厉谴责一切盗版行为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.00,0:02:30.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,C2小精灵工作组正招募翻译校译人员
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.00,0:02:35.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,有日语翻译能力的朋友如有意加入我们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.00,0:02:40.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,请登录论坛后给 {\fnTahoma}smnliu{\r} 发送悄悄话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.00,0:02:47.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,本集宠物小精灵的制作人员是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.00,0:02:50.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,片源 06_taro     原稿 蓝蓝圆企鹅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.00,0:02:53.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,校译 哀小哀 so-nansu     校对 superbabyXP
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.00,0:02:56.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,时间 キンヤ     特效 meimei
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.00,0:02:59.00,other,,0000,0000,0000,,资料 PPK      监督 smnliu & SAP
